[
{"question": "I turned my old thermostat into a smart thermostat with a raspberry pi", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "My Indie Software Projects", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "JSONPerf - Visual, Unbiased and Up-To-Date JSON Performance Benchmark", "details": "", "answers": ["I had some free time so I created a benchmark of JSON libraries.\nMultiple blog posts are discussing JSON serializing and deserializing  performance but they are always correct only for the time they were posted.I wanted to have a single, updating place for all programmers that need to decide what library to use when they start a new project and performance is a consideration.TL;DR: Currently, JSONPerf supports Python 3 and Python 2.\nAdditional languages will be supported in the near future.Another useful feature - you can benchmark using your JSON file.If most of the JSONs you deal with are in a certain structure, use that feature as it will tell you how different packages deal with your structure of JSONs.Link: \nSource: Would love to hear your thoughts / questions!"]},
{"question": "This programmer reverse engineered the Pfizer mRNA vaccine source code", "details": "", "answers": ["The article was way better than the (editoralized) Reddit post title would lead one to suspect.Thinking of DNA/RNA as a programming code with file headers etc. is funny, but even without that the breakdown and high level explanation of the different segments was great."]},
{"question": "How to build beautiful plots with Python and Seaborn", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Edmund Clarke, Turing Award winner, has died", "details": "", "answers": ["That's disappointing to hear :( He taught one of my courses at CMU a long time ago, and he once brought chocolate for the class. The chocolate candy was stuffed inside his , which he then passed around class."]},
{"question": "What are Closures? How are they implemented in C#? How do they \u201ccapture\u201d environment variables from different scopes? What are the side effects you weren\u2019t aware of? Let\u2019s get some practical intuition inspecting the IL code as a source of truth.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "A few months ago I posted my coding project here, a basic application that track my mood to help me with managing my ADHD. Today I got around to bringing it online and inviting my first users to try it out. Thanks for your support r/coding, the response from this community was amazing.", "details": "", "answers": ["Looks really cool! I know you're just starting out, but just a little thought - I would caution against making claims about measuring medications' effectiveness, or giving anything that could be construed as advice, without a big fat disclaimer on your site along the lines of \"THIS APP DOES NOT PROVIDE MEDICAL ADVICE.\""]},
{"question": "Abusing my computer science knowledge to cheat at Catan", "details": "", "answers": ["Have you tried going non-deterministic?Instead of storing the current state of resource distribution, you store a set of possible states. When resources are added, you add them to each state. When someone steals a resource, you replace each state with all possible successors. When someone discards/spends resources, you remove states that are impossible.Then you can display a set of states eirher by displaying only the things common to all current states, or give the full superposition of that's not too crammed.This approach should always give you all available information without relying on heuristics. The downside is that the state set might blow up, but since there are only 5 resources and in all concurrent states each player has the same amount of total resources, the number of states per player is bounded."]},
{"question": "Your Programming New Year's Resolution", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How To Optimize Javascript Code ?", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Configure Free Wildcard SSL Certificate on AWS Application Load Balancer (ALB) Through Terraform", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Some of my favourites maze generating algorithms implemented using pygame, hope you like it :)", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Complete Python Bootcamp: Go from zero to hero in Python 3", "details": "", "answers": ["I'm guessing that is a torrenting site, where you get copyrighted materials for free."]},
{"question": "About go get and go install in Go 1.16", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Program to print Fibonacci series in C++", "details": "", "answers": ["That's not even the Fibonacchi series, it should begin with 0 1 1..."]},
{"question": "The Top 15 Most Commonly Used AWS Services You Should Know About", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Material design in visual studio Blend", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Writing Good Unit Tests; Don't Mock Database Connections - Qvault", "details": "", "answers": ["There's a strong  aspect to this post..."]},
{"question": "Flutter Canvas Tutorials - A Christmas Greeting Animation", "details": "", "answers": ["Cool stuff, I really like custom canvas logic."]},
{"question": "Building an App for Your Christmas Lights", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Updated Zoom Bot (plays youtube links over zoom) URL", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Comic Mono font", "details": "", "answers": ["i hate that this actually looks great"]},
{"question": "JavaScript Performance In The Wild 2020 - We Rendered A Million Web Pages To Find Out What Makes The Web Slow", "details": "", "answers": ["I guess I need to tell our CTO to upgrade to HTTP/0.9 instead of 3.0, seems like a big preformance gain/joke"]},
{"question": "How to Learn Python Programming", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Why can't I close windows directly from the Alt+Tab interface in Windows Vista? | The Old New Thing", "details": "", "answers": ["It doesn't really explains anything other than saying \"shit's complicated but we've dealt with it (and I will not tell you how)\""]},
{"question": "Germany tops the list of the most desired tech job relocation destinations", "details": "", "answers": ["Germany is great, lived there for a year, but I can't see the tech scene as the reason one would want to move there."]},
{"question": "FSFE Responds to \"I took the FSFE to court\" (quoting wildly different claims on the court's findings)", "details": "", "answers": ["Further, they claim the investigation is in fact still ongoing, but also sayThe court judgement of 19 November 2020 (reference number 42 Ca 5723/20) did not acknowledge any factual basis to the assertions. Furthermore the judges concluded that our former employee's own statements prove that she \u201cneither experienced hostility, nor was she offended, nor in another form intimidated or demeaned\u201d. Additionally they found, she received equal treatment, and that \u201cthe boundaries of socially acceptable conduct\u201d were \u201cnot exceeded\u201d.The original poster of the story has come out with a :Update: It was brought to my attention my interpretation of the court ruling may have been optimistic due to relying on machine translation. Whilst translations may be faulty, they are a small part of my story and my story still stands.Suffice to say, it appears as though the entire story should have been under more scrutiny as I repeatedly suggested within that thread (especially as \"optimistic\" is an understatement)..cc:\n\nE: formatting, original post linkedE: Downvotes on quoted material, only on reddit where whoever first comes to the court of public opinion wins, I suppose."]},
{"question": "Modern Full stack web application development tools setup for web development.", "details": "", "answers": ["Stop doing this full-stack nonsense. Most devs don't need it, despite what hirers make you want to believe."]},
{"question": "I am starting a Big O Notation series. Feedback on how to improve is appreciated.", "details": "", "answers": ["My plan is to create other videos on O(1), On O(n log n) etc. Some questions I am considering:Any feedback is welcomed!"]},
{"question": "AI model shows promise to generate faster, more accurate weather forecasts.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "MicroProfile 4.0 is Now Available", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Top 10 Highest Paying Programming Languages To Learn In 2021", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Infrastructure as Code Explained", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Top 10 CI/CD Pipeline Implementation Challenges And Solutions", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "What causes SyntaxError on live web sites? | CatchJS", "details": "", "answers": ["My favorite is when  users have browser plugins that inject javascript code that raises errors.  A common error to see reported is an error complaining that an 'article' variable can't be found.  Common js error reporting libraries actually have this error filtered from being reported.  I actually went through my code and changed places where I used 'article' as a variable to 'articleObject' because of some crappy add-on that a bunch of users seem to use and I was chasing my tail trying to figure out how my SPA code was causing this issue."]},
{"question": "What is a Pedagogic IDE?", "details": "", "answers": ["Interesting but what about the (comparative) predominance of autodidacts in the field of programming? And if the ide is an aeroplane you still have to learn to fly an aeroplane - you can\u2019t fly a simpler aeroplane you still have to learn a certain largish subset of \u2018aeroplane\u2019 if you want to be an employable pilot"]},
{"question": "Best Programming Language to Learn in 2020", "details": "", "answers": ["Downvoted for massive ad spam / popups. Unreadable."]},
{"question": "Astera 1.0-ish Release - C99 Cross Platform 2D Game Library", "details": "", "answers": ["I like your release model, although perhaps you should invert the logic and call it 1.0-unstable"]},
{"question": "Random Discovery \u2013 A Brief History of DirectX", "details": "", "answers": ["The project was codenamed the Manhattan Project, as in relation to the World War II project of the same name, the idea was to displace the Japanese-developed video game consoles with personal computers running Microsoft's operating system.[5]-- From Wikipedia."]},
{"question": "Exciting Programming Memes", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Cyberpwned: Beating Cyberpunk 2077's hacking minigame in ~50 lines of Python", "details": "", "answers": ["While not the way CDPR intended to play this mini game, this is undoubtedly a more immersive, canonical way to solve these puzzles :B"]},
{"question": "Top 10 Highest Paying Programming Languages To Learn In 2021", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Common security issues with crypto websites and APIs", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "JavaScript Shorthand Techniques that save your life", "details": "", "answers": ["Shorter doesn't always equal better. Writing code that's easy to read is the important thing."]},
{"question": "Parsiq: the Zapier for blockchains", "details": "", "answers": ["Is this satire?"]},
{"question": "I built an issue bounty platform for open source development! (rysolv.com)", "details": "", "answers": ["Been working on  for about 9 months now and finally got it out the door! Anyone can import an issue to the site and contribute towards the bounty. Whoever submits a pull request closing out the issue earns the bounty.My main goal is to bring some more support into open source development, and to encourage new people to contribute to projects.Would love to hear any feedback on the site, or bugs you find!"]},
{"question": "Test Driven Development with JUnit 5. Part 5", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Inferenal Engine - A Tool to Build NodeJS and Web Based Expert Systems", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "In light of the Great Conjunction tonight, I used my software tool, PISES, to go find a naturally occurring (procedurally generated!) GC in a Binary Solar System!", "details": "", "answers": ["Hey everyone! If you found this interesting or would like some insight into how these solar systems are generated and propagated, feel free to check out and subscribe to my blog, ."]},
{"question": "Convert web pages into PDFs with Puppeteer and NodeJS", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "An interactive Breadth First Search Visualizer", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Am i the only programmer listening to opera ?", "details": "", "answers": ["Symphonic Metal is my preference"]},
{"question": "Why the Release of Ruby 3 Will Be Monumental", "details": "", "answers": ["That is a lot of words to say \"I prefer Ruby to other languages\".That's a good reason for the writer to choose Ruby, but I'm disappointed by the lack of examples or demonstrations of the supposed elegance.  I don't think this is helpful for anyone else deciding for or against Ruby, other than to know that there are people out there who really like it."]},
{"question": "Basic Concepts of Programming language", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "An interview with the YipitData team about how they built a self service platform for building analytics products on alternative data sets to power investment strategies.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "AWS Management Gets Easier with AWS CloudShell", "details": "", "answers": ["Why do they limit the regions so much?"]},
{"question": "Cakelisp: a programming language for games (compiled, strong C/C++ interop, compile-time code execution)", "details": "", "answers": ["A simple example is type declarations. In C:const char* myString = \"Blah\";The same variable, in Cakelisp:(var my-string (* (const char)) \"Blah\")I love how compact and easy to read that new language \"C\" is."]},
{"question": "Microsoft Offers Web Development for Beginners", "details": "", "answers": ["If it's anything like their \"Beginner's Series to: JavaScript\"  that they published in October, no thank you.I watched the videos and posted , but it was easily some of the worst beginner JavaScript content I've seen..."]},
{"question": "The \"rm -rf *\" story - insights", "details": "", "answers": ["Jfc testing a remote code execution exploit with rm -rf is kinda like testing to see if a gun is loaded by pointing it at your stomach and pulling the trigger."]},
{"question": "Back to the '70s with Serverless", "details": "", "answers": ["The modern age is only missing GNU Autotools rewritten in Javascript to truly rediscover the joys of configuration as code. Obviously you need a multiplatform build system to build build systems for build systems."]},
{"question": "Real Optimization Problems Can be Solved Using Tiny Quantum Computer.", "details": "", "answers": ["It\u2019s amazing how far we can get without fundamentally understanding what we are doing."]},
{"question": "Learn Big O Notation Graphically", "details": "", "answers": ["Do people really have that much trouble with these concepts?"]},
{"question": "The Ultimate C Guide for Beginners in 2020", "details": "", "answers": ["there is nothing \"Ultimate\" about this If you don't know C, I'd highly recommend you consider it, but this link helps nobody"]},
{"question": "10 Best Programming Languages to Learn in 2021 - Statistics and Data", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How we developed software to solve the problem of counting growing plants", "details": "", "answers": ["And they even didn't tell how they developed the software.Marking as spam."]},
{"question": "Debugging refraction in a ray tracer", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "What Everyone Must Know About On Demand Food Delivery Solutions?", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Innovations That Changed Computer Technology", "details": "", "answers": ["They presented FORTRAN as the first semi-modern programming language. But I would credit : it was born slightly later than FORTRAN, but was much closer to the block-oriented approach used by the likes of C, Java, Pascal, VB, etc. that we usually use today.Algol would probably still would be widely used if it  had improved its I/O functions earlier. For some reason, they couldn't get I/O right. It was 10 years ahead of it's time but its I/O functions were 10 years behind, allegedly due to an \"idealism\" squabble among the standards committee. Some tried to keep I/O abstract, but such often didn't adapt to specific platforms well. Lesson: don't let idealism blind you to practical issues."]},
{"question": "Apple M1 foreshadows Rise of RISC-V", "details": "", "answers": ["Imo it doesn't. The M1 is the result of a deep pocketed company attracting and acquiring top talent and spending a decade on tech. To get risc v to actually unseat arm/apple somone else has to put in the engineering resources. Where is that? Not very soon at the very least."]},
{"question": "Ogre 2: from zero to 3D textured model (C++ library integration)", "details": "", "answers": [" is a commercial-grade open-source graphics rendering engine.To me, Ogre offers a nice alternative to going all-in on your own renderer, or .I wrote this tutorial to make integrating Ogre a much more straightforward task. While it may look daunting to beginners, the skill of integrating 3rd party C/C++ libraries will be valuable for any additional dependencies you decide to integrate.I crossposted here  because I hear Ogre is somewhat popular in academia, so it could be useful for them to see (what I think is) a clear guide."]},
{"question": "Bulk loading into PostgreSQL: Options and comparison", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to Use Enum in C#", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Better Quake strafe-jumping with genetic algorithms (video)", "details": "", "answers": ["I love this video format. No bullshit intros/outros, no cheesy soundtrack, no drama, no memes, just the necessary facts to understand what's going on. Must have taken quite a while to create the presentation and animations, too."]},
{"question": "the Mixin polyglot \"stylesheet\"// Summary of Blog: The problem with todays programming is that paradigm remains a cliche that must bind itself to a whole project. Functions are best constructed by languages suited but one language doesnt suit all functions or whole program.", "details": "", "answers": ["Wtf"]},
{"question": "Announcing packages.redbeardlab.com a public CVMFS repository for common software based on the same technology that CERN uses to distribute software in its datacenter.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Analyzing Solorigate, the compromised DLL file that started a sophisticated cyberattack, and how Microsoft Defender helps protect customers - Microsoft Security", "details": "", "answers": ["Can someone explain to me how the compromised .dll file was upload / used by the application? Wouldn't users have to download the .dll file from a unconventional source? Or have the packet manager be pointing to the incorrect source?"]},
{"question": "Bouncy Castle crypto authentication bypass vulnerability revealed: \"This means that passwords that result in hashes that, for instance, don\u2019t contain bytes between 0x00 and 0x3B match every other password hash that don\u2019t contain them.\"", "details": "", "answers": ["Wow that is embarrassing."]},
{"question": "Why and How to use Feature Toggles", "details": "", "answers": ["Nice article! But it could use nicer formatted code blocks, maybe Gist embeds?"]},
{"question": "Floating-point Number Parsing with Perfect Accuracy at GB/sec (video)", "details": "", "answers": ["I always have an issue when comparing speed of libraries designed not to respect the same constraints. I've no issue with \"look if you don't have to handle locale you can achieve this speed up\", but saying \"I'm x times faster than the standard library\" and only mentioning as an afterthought that locale is not handled seems unfair (and I wonder if the SL doesn't also have to handle dynamic rounding mode choice)That said the locale independent float parsing was overdue and I wonder how much a valid replacement for the SL implementation could be sped up."]},
{"question": ".NET 5.0 on Google Cloud", "details": "", "answers": ["I thought it was some nice integration of GC with .NET 5.But it is just running docker container on GC with .NET 5 inside of it. How is that even worthy of an article?"]},
{"question": "Your domain driven project: Lean software development", "details": "", "answers": ["to be honest I thought it's like this:"]},
{"question": "Selling a Tiny Programming Project", "details": "", "answers": ["Geez, you really blew it. You gave up a residual income of \u00a31.64 every 6 months for a short-term gain of a measly $5,300. You should have hung onto it. In 5 years you would have made over \u00a316!Seriously, though, congratulations. And thanks for the interesting read. This is an area where there isn\u2019t a lot of info around, so it\u2019s fun to see the process."]},
{"question": "ggwave - Tiny data-over-sound library", "details": "", "answers": ["Hi, this is a small C++ library that I developed for transmitting data through sound. It can be used to communicate small bits of data between devices across the room for example. You only need microphone and speakers. Let me know if you have any recommendations for improvement or ideas for interesting applications!"]},
{"question": "I'm creating a text editor and adding a \"Add LINK Tool\" and was wondering, should it automatically add \"http\", or \"https\" before the link? Which one is better to work on most links?", "details": "", "answers": ["I usually use http and assume that any sane website will redirect to the https version on their end."]},
{"question": "No cookie for you - The GitHub Blog", "details": "", "answers": ["Well, good one! Hope more sites follow the example."]},
{"question": "Linux Tips for Beginners", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Why to Learn Python?", "details": "", "answers": ["No"]},
{"question": "How To Get ALL Your Sales Letters Scripts!! Funnel Scripts Webinar Train...", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "This is your brain on code: Researchers decipher neural mechanics of computer programming", "details": "", "answers": ["It's especially surprising because we know there seems to be a crucial period that usually terminates in early adolescence for language acquisition...I thought this was debunked, adults are very capable of learning a second language."]},
{"question": "Merry Christmas! World First Working C++ compiler on Windows that supports all C++20 language features, including Concepts, Modules, Coroutines, Compare, etc.", "details": "", "answers": ["gcc version 11.0.0 20201219 (experimental) (GCC with MCF thread model, built by cqwrteur. Merry Christmas)"]},
{"question": "I made a (free) application that lets you group taskbar shortcuts", "details": "", "answers": ["Recommendation: use github releases instead of versioning an archive of the binary in your repo."]},
{"question": "Airflow 2.0.0", "details": "", "answers": ["Does anyone else get the nagging feeling that there might be an Apache project that does exactly what they need if they'd only take the time to search through all billion of them?"]},
{"question": "Learning Machine Learning | Week 1 | Machine Learning Course | Andrew Ng | Coursera", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "A new Rust cryptography library from Google", "details": "", "answers": ["How is this new when the last commit is 9 months old?"]},
{"question": "RANDOM VISUALS (Android Processing APDE)", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Joomla Adding page breaks", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Alki, or how we learned to stop worrying and love cold metadata", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Unlocking PayPal payments for Nigeria", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Joomla Adding page breaks", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "The best programming problem solving technique", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "SolarWinds breach in mainstream report", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Do you know why IoT and AI make the Perfect Match?", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Rust Survey 2020 Results", "details": "", "answers": ["When we asked respondents to rate their expertise in Rust, there was a clear peak at 7 out of 10. It\u2019s hard to say how this compares across languages but it seems notable that relatively few are willing to claim full expertise.From 2010 to 2020, I went from 0 to 7 in Rust, and from 8 to 4 in C++."]},
{"question": "Blind Date: The Reality of Software Engineers Hiring Process", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Programming Memes!", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Stacks, and how they are used in 8-bit computers based on 6502", "details": "", "answers": ["Few minor nitpicks:\nIt's important to notice that the 6502 stack is a postdecrementing stack, unlike the predecrementing stack used on most other platforms. In other words, the stack pointer points at the first free byte, not at the last pushed byte.\nThe stack is not in the zeroth page in memory, the zero page is. Stack is in page 1. 6502 pages are 256 bytes, not 512. \nYou don't need two pages of memory for a 6502 system. And you don't even need a whole page, Atari 2600 used a cheaper variant of 6502 with only 128 bytes of RAM (mapped to $80-$ff and $180-$1ff simultaneously).\nStack underflow and overflow are not a thing on 6502. The stack will simply wrap around. At most, if the stack overflows, code that tries to address things relative to the stack pointer will misbehave, or some old data pushed to the stack gets overwritten. But if you never use more than 256 bytes of stack, you don't use the stack page for anything else and you don't try to index into the stack, the initial value of the stack pointer and any overflows and underflows are totally irrelevant.\nThe hardware stack on 6502 is a poor place for memory management. Stack allocation and deallocation on 6502 is slow, and the stack is slow to access. Also, the stack is small, so it's risky to store too much data on it. If you need a data stack, it's usually better to have a separate data stack. That's what the CC65 compiler does.\n"]},
{"question": "Learn to Use Email with Git", "details": "", "answers": ["Git ships with built-in tools for collaborating over email. With this guide, you'll be contributing to email-driven projects like the Linux kernel, PostgreSQL, or even git itself in no time."]},
{"question": "Release is giving out free Minecraft servers as a holiday gift for all \ud83c\udf84", "details": "", "answers": ["we have a \u201cStarter\u201d plan that\u2019s freeit's an ad"]},
{"question": "Eclipse 2020-12-4.18.0 released!", "details": "", "answers": [", reason being Windows 10 Defender scanning the JAR files.My immediate thought on reading that was why doesn't IntelliJ have the same problem. Then found out from reading the bug report that it does, but Jetbrains have  with an option to automatically configure exclude filters.Apparently the difference is startup time being several MINUTES instead of 10-20 seconds...The problem has been reported to Microsoft ."]},
{"question": "2020 MDN Web Developer Needs Assessment now available", "details": "", "answers": ["We want accountability at Mozilla. Firing dev teams while clueless executives who'd driven it into terminal decline and irrelevance give themselves a huge pay is asinine."]},
{"question": "Desperately need help, I am trying to figure out how to import order records into Microsoft XAL. I know it\u2019s old and it\u2019s possible no one could help but it\u2019s worth a shot.", "details": "", "answers": ["I won't be of any use to you but your link 404s so maybe try fixing that :)"]},
{"question": "What is a comparative study of programming languages, Go and Scala?", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Kelsey Hightower on the Sourcegraph Podcast (transcript included)", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "React vs Angular vs Vue", "details": "", "answers": ["Another pos article"]},
{"question": "Grow Your Business with Contactless Delivery App", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "TechBath File Interigator, Hex Binary Text Decimal", "details": "", "answers": ["NOW HAS HEXEDITOR BUILT IN File Interigator TechBath\nThis is a very differrent File Compare ProgramYou can look at binary, Hex, Decimal, Text. or all together. You can fastjust with the file timeline, or use fast buttons to move through the files. You also can move quickly to differrent data with the prev next buttons, what these controls do is avoid any typing in of memory addresses etc... The buttons do everything.There are some very unusual compares like interlased, or binary without boundaries. Stacking files. Load Files as you work for multi file compares.the files fileCompare.txt  fileCompare2.txt fileCompare3.txt are generated by the app when you choose the command save compare button, it gives plenty of info about whats differrent in the two files, but it has the 3 lists like carage returns that produce line breaks, edit them in a text ediitori set the file size limit to 599001256 bytes which is plenty about 500mb per file"]},
{"question": "Reducing flaky builds by 18x", "details": "", "answers": ["Very interesting post. There are three techniques here which I think are useful.First, if a test is 'flaky,' rather than bothering the developer who last changed any file in the codebase, the test system assigns an issue to the person who last changed the test. This is about changing the incentives, and centralizing a previously unseen cost.Second, tests are automatically retried. When a test fails, the same test is run a second time. Assuming a test fails randomly 1% of the time, this means that running it twice reduces the failure rate to 0.01%. Of course, not all flaky tests fail randomly. This brings me to the third point.Third, there are three techniques used to try to prove that flaky tests are indeed flaky.If a test both fails and succeeds on the same piece of code, then it shouldn't be trusted as a signal of code quality.One thing I found surprising about this piece is that their commit failure rate hovered between 5% and 25% before they implemented this system. That must have been incredibly irritating."]},
{"question": "Pok\u00e9dex - A React side-project using Pok\u00e9API", "details": "", "answers": ["Cool app! Though I do think stuff like this is off topic for the sub."]},
{"question": "Programming with Functions - a YouTube series about basics of FP", "details": "", "answers": ["Nothing personal against this exact video, but I've been noticing it since I started browsing this sub that there are an awful lot of \"Beginner's guide to FP\" posts that all basically reiterate the same points (immutability is good, you can easily replace parts, less surprises, etc.), but never really go deeper or show more practical examples. I wonder if it's due to a sort of \"hype chasing\" or perhaps that the creators quickly run out of steam and have no idea where to proceed from the basics."]},
{"question": "How the API Graph can Help Bridge the Security/Developer Gap", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "S3 API made possible in a NOSQL database (Cassandra drop-in replacement)", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Preparing VALORANT for launch with load testing", "details": "", "answers": ["I'm surprised that this doesn't have more upvotes here. It is definitely a very interesting and thorough blog post that covers a lot of different areas and subjects."]},
{"question": "How to build a +100 language translation API with machine learning", "details": "", "answers": ["I found it fun to learn some of the ways Google trained their translator code.For example, they would find a web page  and  and assume that one is a translation of the other, especially if things like the same dates or numbers appeared in the same sentences.They also went out to the UN and picked up tens of thousands of pages of professionally translated documents in a variety of world languages."]},
{"question": "There's something off about Open Source", "details": "", "answers": ["The thing about OSS is that it is completely OPEN for use, to look at the code and to change to fit a specific need.  The best thing that could happen is that a business commits to support the OSS project.  Unfortunately, the BUSINESS usually isn't the one making the decision to use an OSS product.  It is usually the employee who has been tasked to do a job and therefore made the decision to obtain OSS and modify it for need.  I've done this on many occasion."]},
{"question": "Apache Flink-powered Machine Learning model serving & real-time feature generation at Razorpay", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "BPF and Go: Modern forms of introspection in Linux", "details": "", "answers": ["What  BPF? Would be good to expand the acronym in the opening"]},
{"question": "FFI-Safe Polymorphism in Rust: Thin Trait Objects", "details": "", "answers": ["I like the author's alternative solution of not doing polymorphism.\u200bRust is a new language, with a new structure that just slightly resembles older languages. You can even do pseudo-scripting with it. I manged to . You can also do complex systems programming with it. You don't need to stretch it too far for both. But what you can't do properly without stretching it is OOP. So why not come up with a different pattern? A new paradigm, a new method? Something that's... new?"]},
{"question": "Why XML Security is Broken", "details": "", "answers": ["So, the title is a bit misleading in the modern context - it's not a holistic treatment of the security implications of XML, but rather a 2004 discussion of the challenges in defining and implementing a XML cryptographic signing framework. As the comments thus far illustrate, most people will read this with a \"compared to X\" sort of a view, with JSON being the modern substitute. I would argue JSON has many of the same issues, if not more.JSON has fewer features. It doesn't have namespaces. It doesn't have complex whitespace treatment. It doesn't have object types. If you need any of those things, you invent them outside of (or layered onto) JSON. That happens more often than you think - it's often implicit, but it is still there.  Encoding stuff is also kinda fucked up. XML has some \"in band\" encoding signalling such as BOM and encoding headers. While JSON is sort-of supposed to be always UTF8 it's not really always, and you get similar complexities in encoding metadata handling. XML has some implementation issues - namely unsafe default behaviour relating to rarely used features - entity expansion and retrieval of supporting referenced documents (like schemas).  Those are implementation issues stemming from the feature complexity of the format, and a reasonable reason to avoid XML if you don't need so many features. With respect to the specific issue of signing, JSON has many of the same issues as XML, wherein the JSON blob is not always what you really want to sign (e.g. do you really care about  which whitespace characters are used, or the order of the object properties?) , although because of its fewer features the problem is less complex. "]},
{"question": "Swap \u21cb v0.3.0 \u00b7 Vapor Cryptocurrency is now available for cross-chain atomic swap.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "The story of the one line fix", "details": "", "answers": ["Is the last question rhetorical? I don\u2019t really understand the point the author is trying to make."]},
{"question": "How to learn programming in 30 days", "details": "", "answers": ["Anyone claiming that you can \"learn programming in 30 days\" is talking BS."]},
{"question": "How I Learned to Manage My Small Team of Devs and So Can You", "details": "", "answers": ["Before assigning each feature to a dev, first make sure there won\u2019t be a need to change anythingI mean what world do some devs live in where things are set in stone at the start of a project."]},
{"question": "CSS Naming Conventions that Will Save You Hours of Debugging", "details": "", "answers": ["Going one by one through the article's suggestions:Use Hyphen Delimited StringsYeah okThe BEM Naming ConventionBEM is dumb and it's just poorly replicates what you can already do through CSS selectors.  Instead of having the abomination stick-man__feet as a class name, just use .stick-man .feet as your selector.Use js- class namesDon't mix CSS and Javascript concerns in the first place.  If your Javascript is referring to elements by CSS class for any reason other than manipulating those classes, you've screwed this up.Use the Rel attributeNo.  No no no.  The rel attribute is only valid on four elements, and it has  on those elements.  It's not an attribute you should be just throwing on every element because you're allergic to data, nor is it an attribute you should be assigning your own pidgin invalid values into.Don\u2019t use data attributesWhy the hell not?  That's what data attributes are ."]},
{"question": "Advent of Code 2020 - Day10", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Tips to stay focused and finish your hobby project - Stack Overflow Blog", "details": "", "answers": ["Tip#0: Don't have ADHD."]},
{"question": "Emacs from scratch. TOO AWESOME", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Content consumption has become an all-inclusive activity: a pipeline to knowledge and enjoyment, but one that often requires trimming through a forest of tangents and clickbait. Can technology solve this problem?", "details": "", "answers": ["Yes, provided whoever is programming the algorithm can do so without bias."]},
{"question": "Hello Everyone, I started learning react and here is the first website I developed about Corona Virus. I really work hard on this website and any comment is appreciated. My goal is to improve my react and web design skills. So let me know what you think :)", "details": "", "answers": ["It's really good for a beginner site. Good color contrast, conveyed information is clear and straightforward. You should put it on GitHub if you want feedback on your actual code though. Slight nitpick: the table has a horizontal scrollbars on mobile, and it can totally fit the full width on screen"]},
{"question": "Minimal safe Bash script template", "details": "", "answers": ["I trust people to write safe shell scripts even less than I trust them to write safe C programs."]},
{"question": "U.S. Treasury, Commerce Depts. Hacked Through SolarWinds Compromise", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How toxic is your code?", "details": "", "answers": ["Lets redefine yet another word that has a definition for our blog post in an attempt to be known as the person who defined it that way!"]},
{"question": "Welcome Yari: MDN Web Docs has a new platform", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Windows Task Manager Source Code Review by Original Author: Retired Microsoft Engineer \"davepl\"", "details": "", "answers": ["Just learnt through this video that pressing and holding f5 in task manager does refresh it much quicker on windows 10! I have been a windows user all along and I never knew that! \ud83d\ude05\ud83d\ude02"]},
{"question": "How to Migrate Data In MongoDB", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Types of Apps that can be built with Angular Framework", "details": "", "answers": ["Square ones, triangular ones, but not oval or circular!"]},
{"question": "A defer mechanism for C \u2013 Jens Gustedt's Blog", "details": "", "answers": ["It's interesting idea, but IMO, its use would be severely hampered by the absence of anonymous functions/lambdas. One of the reasons defer feels nice to use in Go is because you can define the cleanup routine right there along with the rest of the code. Doing cleanup in an anonymous function also means that the cleanup routine has easy access to any other function-scoped variables.FWIW, both GCC and Clang implement a variable attribute called __cleanup__  right now, if you're in a situation which permits the use of compiler extensions."]},
{"question": "A Comprehensive Guide To Genetic Algorithms \u2014 The ELI5 Way", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Instantly search 28M books from OpenLibrary (weekend project using Typesense Search InstantSearch.js)", "details": "", "answers": [" I built this from the OpenLibrary (Internet Archive) books dataset ().Thank you  from Internet Archive, for helping me get access to the data quickly and giving me pointers about the schema.I should add - I built this in about 12 hours as a weekend project, so there might be some lurking issues.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n"]},
{"question": "MicroProfile Java Microservices on WildFly - Piotr's TechBlog", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "On Using Apple Silicon Mac mini for Continuous Integration", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Sorting Algorithm Stability - What it is and When it Matters", "details": "", "answers": ["Barely scrtatches the surface."]},
{"question": "Writing a LaTeX algebraic expression parser in C++ (Part 1)", "details": "", "answers": ["Hello , I have been working on this LaTeX algebraic expression parser for the last few months and would like to proceed with open-sourcing the project. The purpose of this project is to ingest a LaTeX string to achieve the goals of evaluating, expanding, simplifying, and solving. Thus far I have the first two goals complete, with simplifying and solving yet to be implemented.I have recently spun up my domain of \"mathemat.io\" to provide a frontend for this library, and hopefully one day provide a fully-functional free alternative to the likes of Symbolab and WolframAlpha. Examples include the following:Please visit the project here on GitHub: Any and all suggestions are greatly appreciated.As a side note, subsequent blog posts further detailing the various procedures of the library will be made.Thank you all for your time."]},
{"question": "Page Fault Injection in Virtual Machines: Accessing Swapped-Out Memory from the Hypervisor", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Recursion Tree Visualizer for Python", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Wrote up a set of Dockerfile best-practices based on my experience over the past 7 years with shipping Docker images. Feedback very appreciated!", "details": "", "answers": ["Most of my Docker experience has been using python. I have found that specifying the Docker image's hash gives the most reliable results when multiple team members can be building and using the container (local dev).I have seen an issue where the python:3.7.2 container was updated without the patch version being bumped. Some underlying Debian libs were updated. One of these libs happened to be the OpenSSL lib... This in turn broke some of our python dependencies and slowed our team down for over an hour while we tried to figure out why the same python image version on multiple machines acted completely differently.If this had happened in a CI system that did not have robust error checking it could have taken down production. Assuming that the CI is building the container and not just deploying it.\u200bOther than that I really like the example container!"]},
{"question": "How to securely implement OAuth in Ruby on Rails", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "SubReddits Every Developer should follow", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Basic patterns programs in C++", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Lazy loading in React", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Getting started with C programming: a lightning fast start for absolute beginners", "details": "", "answers": ["it says:You\u2019ll use Unix-style terminal emulators and command-line tools to execute commands, Linux-style package managers to install programs and libraries, the GNU nano text editor to write C code, the meson build system to build executable programs and the Gtk+ library to write portable, cross-platform graphical programs. This is a big setup for helloe-world.  A bit offputting, I suggest."]},
{"question": "Node.js Development Company in Cochin, India", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Running Piranha Nano on Azure Functions using Custom Handlers", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Wrote an easily hackable template repo for injecting user defined C/C++ functions in a MariaDB docker image", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Learn Git visually.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Simple recursion visualizer for Python", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "400+ Cryptocurrency Historical Data (Open, High, Low, Close) since 2013", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Don't let collation versions corrupt your PostgreSQL indexes (cross-post from r/postgresql)", "details": "", "answers": ["This looks painful, so I didn't read it, but I'm glad there are people out there taking care of it."]},
{"question": "How To Add Dark Mode To Your ReactJS App Using Hooks", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Aiming for correctness with types [with HTTP as an example]", "details": "", "answers": ["Rust is my favorite language and all of my software for the past few years has been implemented in it, but this article is pretty silly. There are Rust HTTP servers which make the same/similar choices as Go's net/http. In addition, there are non-stdlib Go HTTP servers which will make some of the choices you highlight in Hyper. Node has a few alternative choices as well, although I admit they are fewer than Go or Rust. It's not really a drawback of Go  to lose the stdlib ecosystem if you don't like how the stdlib server works - Rust is completely fragmented already. There are plenty of of fairer comparisons between languages other than one's (opinionated but quite solid) stdlib HTTP server vs. a third party server in a language without a real standard.On the subject of language correctness, I will say that while I believe Rust's approach is fantastic for a lot of the software I work on (low-level libraries), it's of course always a spectrum. Haskell people have often told me similar things you are saying about Go/JavaScript for guaranteeing correctness - \"I can't imagine programming in something which provides so few guarantees!\"."]},
{"question": "Artificial intelligence-based algorithm for the early diagnosis of Alzheimer's: Machine-learning algorithm detects early stages of Alzheimer's through functional magnetic resonance imaging", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Intel releases new machine programming tool to detect bugs in code - SD Times", "details": "", "answers": ["It would be nice if the article included some substantive discussion of what distinguishes this static analysis tool from all the others out there."]},
{"question": "Top 10 Features of Python Every Developer Should Know", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Recoil.js - State management for React", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to make an automatic Reddit Link Poster", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Language Agnostic Explained", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Agent programming and instrumentation", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "I've recreated the iFunny Captions generator", "details": "", "answers": ["Out of curiosity, anyone want to enlighten the rest of us why this was downvoted"]},
{"question": "JUMP GAME Leetcode Explanation/walkthrough", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Plutovg v0.1.0 released.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "The secret history of windows task manager. Dave Plummer.", "details": "", "answers": ["Since this is , worth noting that if you hang in there until Episode 3 of this series I do a full code review of the original Windows source code to Task Manager.This video is part of a lecture I gave last night at the University of Regina to help celebrate CSWeek (and Grace Hopper's Birthday!)"]},
{"question": "Kadanes algorithm Explained in Layman Terms", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Virtual Job Interviews: A Short Primer", "details": "", "answers": ["TL;DR: Know how video calls work."]},
{"question": "Sleeping Soundly and Leaving the Lights on: How Noom\u2019s Engineering Team Prepares for the Holidays", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Not a good look for cybersecurity company FireEye, hacked and hacking tools stolen...", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Cartoon illustrations of git concepts like rebase and merge, which seasoned developers understand, but for those unfamiliar with git, these visuals increase understanding", "details": "", "answers": ["Paid ebook. There's already tons of free documentation and examples out there...."]},
{"question": "No software, no cries", "details": "", "answers": ["To clarify the title:  is a Bob Marley song. Emphasis mine:The title and main refrain, \"No Woman, No Cry\", means \"Woman,  cry\". The lyric is sometimes misunderstood outside Jamaica to mean \"if there is no woman, there is no reason to cry\". The lyric is rendered \"No, woman, nuh cry\" in Jamaican patois.I was hoping for a deep dive into exception handling and why raising exceptions to the end user via GUI dialog box is useless. No software, nuh cry. Only Result <T, E>The article is actually about Salesforce's \"No Software\" tagline. It's informative, but only a little bit. I'm not sure what the conclusion or takeaway was supposed to be. Maybe that \"No null\" or \"No threads, no locks, only Rapture\" is a better way to sell Rust and its async runtimes than \"Fearless concurrency\"?"]},
{"question": "Dolphin Progress Report: October and November 2020", "details": "", "answers": ["To be completely honest with our readers, we really wanted to get this one merged before the end of the last progress report when Nintendo's very own emulator in Super Mario 3D All Stars was discovered to share the same bug. After all, we  the fix and knew it would make for some good screenshots. But alas, unfortunate hindrances like  and  got in the way of our devious plan.Ugh, I hate doing my job! /sSadly, Nintendo managed to patch the debug cubes a few days before we did. But that's ok. As their GameCube emulator has a catalog of effectively one game, they didn't have to worry about regression testing the way we have to. It's fine, we're not mad. It wasn't fair so it doesn't count.lel"]},
{"question": "Which is the best code-language to start with?", "details": "", "answers": ["While I do like a Datsun Z, I'm not sure what this post is about..."]},
{"question": "Deno 1.6 supports compiling TypeScript to a single executable", "details": "", "answers": ["Just FYI: it's not compilation in the sense of turning readable code into machine code. It just embeds your TS sources verbatim at the end of the executable."]},
{"question": "The era of the JVM is coming to an end", "details": "", "answers": ["Almost nothing in here is about the JVM.Say you write a small command-line utility function in Java that has dependencies on a few jars. How does one package and distribute this utility? One could look at StackOverflow to see which plugin of your favorite build system is currently popular to create a Fat Jar. However, the official 'Java way' to package your code and its dependencies is still the good old .war file. A faster moving organization would have acknowledged how users like to ship their code. They would have extended the .jar file format (or introduced a new file format) to be able to package dependencies in a standardized manner. But no such thing on the horizon with Java.That's not about the JVM.  That's about the Java ecosystem and specifically how bytecode is packaged and delivered.Project Valhalla, which was supposed to introduce 'Value Types' to Java, was announced back in 2014 and still has no release date. This is about Java the language, not the JVM.Project Loom, which brings green threads, was announced in 2018 and is in a similar state. See above.Want to interop with native code, one still has to deal with the insanity of 20-year-old JNI interfaces.Ah, okay, I stand corrected, we've got one thing about the JVM!  Of course, for most folks it's pretty irrelevant.  I don't remember the last time I wrote my own native code bindings.  Such is the joy of having such a massive Java library ecosystem.Java's Achilles heel after all is the need to maintain backward compatibility. This is about Java the language, not the JVM.I won't bother with the rest.The author seems to have trouble distinguishing between the Java language, the Java ecosystem, and the Java Virtual Machine.Of course, I also think the rest of the article is pretty laughable.  People have been predicting the death of Java the language for at least a couple of decades and it ain't gone yet.  I will happily make a cash bet that 10 years from now Java the language will be around and the Java Virtual Machine will be as relevant as ever."]},
{"question": "Apache Flink 1.12.0 is out with Kubernetes-based HA (High Availability)", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Adobe just released the last Flash update ever", "details": "", "answers": ["Is anyone else a little concerned that the last update is December, but it'll no longer keep working in January? Are we now proudly announcing we're intentionally breaking working software?"]},
{"question": "[RFC] Change Control Manifesto - Keeping clean change history for the FOSS projects", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "WebAuthn: A Guide To Authenticate Your Application", "details": "", "answers": ["Your blog is very informative and to the point."]},
{"question": "Common Expression Language, mutation free C/C++/Java/JavaScript style language", "details": "", "answers": ["How do you write an accumulative loop, a mainstay of algol-family languages, without mutation?"]},
{"question": "Is storing device ids of users device legal?", "details": "", "answers": ["Why I couldn't post without attaching a link?? This is a stupid rule!"]},
{"question": "Rust Data Structures and Algorithms", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to Setup Previews For PRs on Your GitHub Repo Using Netlify", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "kubectl create pizza", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Loosely Coupled Monolith vs Tightly Coupled Microservices", "details": "", "answers": ["This is a good approach and is to be encouraged, but it's not microservices. It's just dependency injection. Not that that is a bad thing."]},
{"question": "Beautyhand", "details": "", "answers": ["error on load\u200b```redux.js:600 Uncaught TypeError: Cannot read property 'apply' of undefinedat redux.js:600at u (redux.js:79)at Module.70 (store.js:9)at l ((index):1)at t ((index):1)at Array.r [as push] ((index):1)at main.ad179ba5.chunk.js:1```"]},
{"question": "How I stopped hating Test Driven Development", "details": "", "answers": ["I just give up and mock everything and my test coverage has gone way up.I can code my tests ahead of time knowing it won\u2019t be a nightmare to get to green.Also, I just read the article and it\u2019s very unsubstantial. It\u2019s basically blog spam."]},
{"question": "Why FP Matters - Part 1 \ud83d\udc18 - A brief introduction", "details": "", "answers": ["but i just want smalltalk"]},
{"question": "PKCE: What it is and how to use it with OAuth 2.0", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Technical Interviewer's Checklist", "details": "", "answers": ["Pretty good! "]},
{"question": "paperai: AI-powered literature discovery and review engine for medical/scientific papers", "details": "", "answers": ["paperai is an AI-powered literature discovery and review engine for medical/scientific papers. paperai helps automate tedious literature reviews allowing researchers to focus on their core work. Queries are run to filter papers with specified criteria. Reports powered by extractive question-answering are run to identify answers to key questions within sets of medical/scientific papers.paperai was used to analyze the COVID-19 Open Research Dataset (CORD-19), winning multiple awards in the CORD-19 Kaggle challenge."]},
{"question": "F2P real-time multiplayer turn-based strategy game: Foo vs. Bar", "details": "", "answers": ["Isn't it either realtime  turn-based? Looks like an oxymoron to me."]},
{"question": "RenderMan: An Advanced Path Tracing Architecture for Movie Rendering", "details": "", "answers": ["In opengl cube maps use the renderman coordinate system, which makes no sense at all because opengl uses a different coordinate system."]},
{"question": "obs-cli: Remote control OBS from the command line", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "I shared a \"survival guide\" with tips on how to not get distracted while you code (looking for feedback!)", "details": "", "answers": ["Lets be real, you can't be productive 100% of the time. Coding is a creative process and you can't always force creativity. So thinking or hoping for 100% productivity is just setting yourself up for dissapointment. Days when I'm really inspired I find I spend very little time on distractions, days with less inspiration perhaps some more.In the end a lot of these things are personal. I don't mind my phone being on my desk in front of me. Just like the urge to just wander around the internet, to me it comes down to discipline. With working from home when other people are in the house it's matter of making them understand they can't just walk in or do something loud and annoying. Headphones are one thing, but they need to understand that during workhours not everything is possible."]},
{"question": "Programming career: not everyone is a manager (and that's OK)", "details": "", "answers": ["You couldn't pay me enough to have my managers schedule. 30/40 hours are meetings, no thanks"]},
{"question": "Simulating the universe in a computer", "details": "", "answers": ["Is this about the simulation we live in? Or a simulation within that? Or a simulation within that? Or a..."]},
{"question": "The Google My Business API just changed all of the unique IDs across their reviews API with no warning or notice to developers.", "details": "", "answers": ["This always seems relevant with GAPIsDear RECIPIENT,Fuck yooooouuuuuuuu. Fuck you, fuck you, Fuck You. Drop whatever you are doing because it\u2019s not important. What is important is OUR time. It\u2019s costing us time and money to support our shit, and we\u2019re tired of it, so we\u2019re not going to support it anymore. So drop your fucking plans and go start digging through our shitty documentation, begging for scraps on forums, and oh by the way, our new shit is COMPLETELY different from the old shit, because well, we fucked that design up pretty bad, heh, but hey, that\u2019s YOUR problem, not our problem.We remain committed as always to ensuring everything you write will be unusable within 1 year.Please go fuck yourself,-- "]},
{"question": "Everything about software UI is changing. Here's what UI developers can do to keep up.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Is Ruby 3 Actually Three Times Faster?", "details": "", "answers": ["TLDR: \u201cBroadly speaking \u2018yes\u2019, but...\u201dWell worth the read though for a good discussion."]},
{"question": "Can someone help me understand how to plot a graph of a projectile in GNUplot with initial velocity and angle given?(Fortran code for the same is attached.)", "details": "", "answers": ["Do the needful"]},
{"question": "Systems Performance: Enterprise and the Cloud, 2nd Edition (2020)", "details": "", "answers": ["Why was this posted without comment?"]},
{"question": "Consafe Logistics Using Ada for Critical Warehouse Control System Firmware", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Hi everyone, i'm a 15 year old gamedev. I just released the Launch Trailer for my 3d game called Beanus, if you could check it out that would mean a lot :)", "details": "", "answers": ["That screaming dude missing a jump is why i would not want to check it out. Show more gameplay in the trailer and remove that screamer."]},
{"question": "Everybody was cargo culting - My personal experience to jump off the bandwagon (effect)", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Enterprise secret management is no easy task - who are the major players?", "details": "", "answers": ["Just checked out Akeyless Vault after reading this article. It looks like a good alternative - Kubernetes does not handle secrets well out of the box."]},
{"question": "Twitch chat controlled lego train, written in JS, Created by my software engineering class", "details": "", "answers": ["Pretty cool!! Would do well in your projects section for your resume."]},
{"question": "Localizing Your Chrome Extension: An Easy Tutorial", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Discovering Value - How SCRUM-Project-thinking causes valueless feature mills", "details": "", "answers": ["When working with a Scrum Team you will be aware that there is an emphasis on delivering value. This idea is a differentiator for Agile delivery. We deliver valuable outcomes. We deliver increments of valuable software. We deliver the most valuable thing first.I've yet to actually experience this.  All SCRUM is used for at my company is making sure we get our stuff checked in on time."]},
{"question": "A gentle introduction to Kubernetes (short: K8s)", "details": "", "answers": ["Hey dude.. come here for a sec.....Wanna learn some kubernetes?"]},
{"question": "Breaking the iframe frontier: ibridge", "details": "", "answers": ["First sentence has a spelling error:I forked postmate and called it ibrige.Note the last word. There is at least one more like it.pre stablishThat's not English."]},
{"question": "The True Meaning of Technical Debt \ud83d\udcb8", "details": "", "answers": ["Putting aside the fact that functional programming has been shown to produce fewer faults in software compared to some of the more imperative forms the article puts forward as alternative, in my opinion, communication should assume the person reading the code has the necessary general understanding of the language -- which should eliminate the \"can they understand this construct here?\" problem. I, personally, am against \"unrolling\" code to make it readable to people who are assumed to, well, not know the language enough. Systems in production aren't tutorials teaching the language. Also, people who write or contribute to systems that deal with, I don't know, transactions, should probably be trusted with and expected to know both the system language and the domain language. In fact, I would imagine it is a reasonable belts-and-suspenders assurance they will not introduce undesirable and unnecessary faults into a production system, unless they know enough to read the code, save for being explained the coding style and whatever idiosyncracy the code demonstrates beyond generic patterns the language typically employs.I don't understand this argument that is often brought forth that we should \"dumb down\" code so that the uninformed and unitiated should be able to grok it. I do think people should be taught the ropes of an organization and whatever unique code style it adopts where they work, but the responsibility of knowing enough Ruby in order to use it, should be on the person, and the code owner should not need to lower the bar. The height of the bar is also a subjective measure.Imperative coding style has been demonstrated to far more easily allow for off-by-one errors at least, are we going to bill the people who can't be bothered to learn some functional programming paradigms, for the faults such errors introduce? And also have developers who  offer a different, potentially beneficial if \"less readable\" (for the \"uninitiated\", mind you) coding style that may produce fewer faults, sneer at the overly-verbose code, instead? Tersity is not always obfuscation, I'd argue.Also, I do prefer explicit to implicit (and have learned to do so by experience) but I think the article mixes it up with \"dumbing down\" code, which I find are not one and the same thing at all. \"Explicit\" does not mean \"anyone who has ever read 100 lines of Python code should be able to pick up this code and work on it\". After all, there is always something \"implicit\" in every system and programming language environment, by extension. The bar should and can of course be set by the team, but it's also the team that will be evaluating how many more (potentially not skilled enough) developers they can enable to work on the code base by in turn re-factoring the code into more elemental/primitive/\"readable\" constructs. It's a matter of preference and a form of cost saving measure I guess, at the end of the day. But every book demands a certain level of reading proficiency, to provide its own value."]},
{"question": "The Biggest Unsolved Problems in Computer Science", "details": "", "answers": ["I like how people always forget cache invalidation in these lists. Sure P vs NP is super important but finding a provable optimal way to do cache invalidation would be invaluable"]},
{"question": "Functional TypeScript With fp-ts", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Python Generators: The In-depth Article You've Always Wanted - Python kitchen", "details": "", "answers": ["Thanks for the read! Legitimately, did not know that you can send values back to a generator."]},
{"question": "GitHub Dark Mode is too Dark. Here's the mathematical proof", "details": "", "answers": ["It's an interesting observation and analysis, but it can be difficult to assign absolute correct thresholds and values. The font weight also shifts the balance.One thing that looks unappealing is the blueish cast to github, for both foreground and background. I prefer a touch warmer foregrounds contrasted by generally cooler backgrounds (peach on blue if you really blew up the saturation). This adds some color-contrast to reduce the need for overall brightness. I really dislike the light-on-dark schemes which have eye-blazing contrast-levels.I don't really use github, but out of curiosity I checked against the colorscheme I've lived with and tuned for the past 20+ years. It's surprisingly similar to github's levels, but githubs are slightly more drab. In particular, those diff backgrounds look pretty muddy. Mine are similar brightness, but just a touch more saturation to distinguish them (especially that green really is tending to gray!).That secondary foreground color does seem too dim -- what is used for? I think all of my foreground colors are similar contrast-level as my normal foreground, but different shades. Maybe my brownish comments are slightly dimmer, but still not as dim as that github secondary.I guess, depending on the font, I might also feel like github is overall \"too dark\". I tried to check, but maybe I need to be signed in to switch to dark mode. \"Bah humbug\" to the web."]},
{"question": "Magento vs Prestashop: Which Should You Use for Your Next eCommerce Website", "details": "", "answers": ["Neither. Bloated lock-in 'platforms' full of features you don't need but for which you are paying"]},
{"question": "TCR Practice in TypeScript", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Docker Can Spare you a lot of Headaches with Test Databases", "details": "", "answers": ["Docker is pretty nice for this, for our integration tests we'd spin up a mongo container and run API tests against it (connection, speed, storage, correctness, etc). The advantage is definitely that you dont need to deal with in memory issues (although that has its advantages too) and its very easy to do."]},
{"question": "Advent of Code 2020 - Day 7", "details": "", "answers": ["subscribed! I love these kinds of videos"]},
{"question": "Former Uber engineer shares \u201cbiggest engineering disaster\u201d story", "details": "", "answers": ["this is sad and fascinating at the same time. I can't imagine the burnouts of the people who were stuck with typing one letter and waiting 45 seconds. sometimes my vscode takes a second and it makes me wanna kill myself. yet I'm fascinated by the people that kept it going."]},
{"question": "I tried to make the fastest sorting algorithm I could think of... in rust. It ended up being kinda fast, but I'd be grateful for some feedback :)", "details": "", "answers": ["That is kind of a degenerate case of a radix sort, with a radix the size of the value-range. I used such a thing for software rendering in the past, basically sorting vertical spans into their appropriate scanline \"by inspection\". More like \"you belong here\" than a sort. :)A normal radix sort will use some radix less than the full span of values, like 16 or 256. This requires multiple passes to fully resolve, but it scales better across wide ranging values."]},
{"question": "Be Good at Referencing, Not Remembering", "details": "", "answers": ["For anyone who works on software that covers fairly broad swaths of problem domains, you just can't remember it all anyway. Being good at finding (or re-finding) the answers is one of the key skills of a good developer. But of course too many job interviews are testing you for exactly the opposite, your ability to trivia game show style regurgitate memorized factoids (as has been discussed ad nauseum here but, hey, why not do it again?)"]},
{"question": "Data records in OOP", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Getting started with C programming: a lightning fast start for absolute beginners", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "GetHashCode() Pitfalls in C#", "details": "", "answers": ["gethashcode is a function that most developers shouldn\u2019t implement themselvesWhat a load of bullshit. There are 2, maybe 3 basic rules to know. It\u2019s not hard to get right. It\u2019s even easier now with the BCL hashcode tooling"]},
{"question": "Star Wars - Episode CCLVI - TIC80 intro in 256 bytes", "details": "", "answers": [""]},
{"question": "Creating a Chrome Extension with React and TypeScript", "details": "", "answers": ["The downfall of Javascript together: Chrome and React. Also a novel example of two things that started wonderful, beautiful, simple, elegant and ended... well, we all know. Next we'll have: \"creating Chrome extensions in Electron\""]},
{"question": "5 Programming Languages That Will Dominate 2021: Python, Go, More", "details": "", "answers": ["Direct link if you want to skip Google News: "]},
{"question": "New research has shown robots can encourage humans to take greater risks in a simulated gambling scenario than they would if there was nothing to influence their behaviors.", "details": "", "answers": ["\"WHAT IS MY PURPOSE?\"\"You goad people into gambling more.\"\"OH GOD\""]},
{"question": "Building a garbage-free network stack for Kafka streams", "details": "", "answers": ["We had a product based on Netty (yeah I know, different stack entirely) that would absolutely choke under load, until Netty 4 which introduced pooled byte buffers and reference counting so you could pass them along without constant copying. I can't believe the stack made it into wide use for 3 prior major versions without ever having been tested in such conditions.Anyway, I'm quite familiar with the problem of typical Java programming idioms getting in the way of efficient performance, so I'm feeling these folks' pain. Glad they were able to get a solution.Java development attitude of creating lots of garbage, and not bothering to pool (for the sake of memory - obv. network connection pooling is still a big deal) is fine and everything, it gets the job done, until you hit certain inflection points and the GC is working like mad to keep up. Trying to structure your application differently rarely works because the entire Java ecosystem generally follows this philosophy, so the libs and frameworks you depend on end up defeating you anyway."]},
{"question": "Kid explains his code to his mom. Insane.", "details": "", "answers": ["It doesn't seem like he understands the code fully. Still, he understands it enough to know what functions do what. Something tells me he copied the code and then explained it. Perhaps I'm just a bit cynical though..."]},
{"question": "When hacking Windows machines, I get tired of constantly googling commands or scrolling through cheat sheets. So to fix that, I made WADComs! It's an interactive cheat sheet for Windows/AD commands with filters. Please contribute your own commands too!", "details": "", "answers": ["I use a keystroke launcher (Launchy) like Spotlight. It basically gives you quick access wherever you are by hitting alt+spacebar (I use it to open URLs, define words, calculator, open apps, etc.) It has 3rd party add-on support. I wonder if there's potential there to quickly bring up your commands."]},
{"question": "How the Slowest Computer Programs Illuminate Math\u2019s Fundamental Limits", "details": "", "answers": ["The busy beaver game asks: Given a certain number of rules, what\u2019s the maximum number of steps that a Turing machine can take before halting?\n[...]The Goldbach conjecture [...] asks whether every even integer greater than 2 is the sum of two primes.\n[...]In 2015, [code was published] for a 27-rule Turing machine that halts if \u2014 and only if \u2014 the Goldbach conjecture is false.\n[...]If it were possible to compute BB(27), that would provide a ceiling on how long we\u2019d have to wait for the Goldbach conjecture to be settled automatically. That\u2019s because BB(27) corresponds to the maximum number of steps this 27-rule Turing machine would have to execute in order to halt (if it ever did). If we knew that number, we could run the Turing machine for exactly that many steps. If it halted by that point, we\u2019d know the Goldbach conjecture was false. But if it went that many steps and didn\u2019t halt, we\u2019d know for certain that it never would \u2014 thus proving the conjecture true.Blew my mind"]},
{"question": "CS 6120: Advanced Compilers: The Self-Guided Online Course", "details": "", "answers": ["Oh, this looks like a fantastic resource, thank you."]},
{"question": "Warhammer 40,000 The New Edition - Trailer (Remastered 8K 60FPS) Resolution increased using neural networks to 8K 60FPS", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "[Solution]CPU Usage Is Too High In Your Program", "details": "", "answers": ["You could  just use :Function: int pthread_cond_clockwait (pthread_cond_t *cond, pthread_mutex_t *mutex,\nclockid_t clockid, const struct timespec *abstime) Preliminary: | MT-Safe | AS-Unsafe lock | AC-Unsafe lock | See POSIX Safety Concepts.Behaves like pthread_cond_timedwait except the time abstime is measured against the clock specified by clockid rather than the clock specified or defaulted when pthread_cond_init was called. Currently, clockid must be either CLOCK_MONOTONIC or CLOCK_REALTIME.And keep the monotonic clock (which should be more resilient to stuff like NTP stepping time on machine)"]},
{"question": "Become shell literate", "details": "", "answers": ["I like this article a lot, as an opinion piece, but it seems very subjective.   I don't really think the shell is quite that critical, beyond the basics every dev is already going to pick up whether they want to or not.If I had to restore deleted files without changing anything else, and finesse was not important, I'd most likely just back everything up, make a copy of everything,  check out the last commit that had the missing files, drag and drop the whole directory over, click \"write into\", and then when it asked if I wanted to overwrite an existing file, I'd click to skip all.Then I'd verify the results with git cola and commit.If it wasn't a very rare one-off task, or the repo was so big that I didn't want to copy everything, I'd probably want to script it, but I'd just use Python, and the result would probably be more readable and easier to modify, especially by other people. I'm not sure how exactly those tarballs for that game work, but I would (If my friend was also a GUI fan) just make a special folder for sharing with them, and sync it with SyncThing, and only send the changed files, with compression enabled, all automatically, regardless of their IP address, plus, SyncThing is awesome for lots of other stuff.Maybe you can write a bash script faster than I can do it the GUI way, but I doubt I can.  It's easy to make mistakes and lose data with bash.  To prevent that, you have to be careful, and the added caution (Or once-a-year screwups that take the whole day to fix) eat into your time savings.You can be incredibly efficient on the CLI. You can be almost as efficient on GUI. Both have other benefits with different levels of importance to different people."]},
{"question": "In the middle of MS Word from the MS Office package can be created automatically", "details": "", "answers": ["Can you help with the answer?"]},
{"question": "Investigating Memory Leaks with Dynamic Expression Trees and EF Core", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Docker installation and proper configuration guide | Explained well", "details": "", "answers": ["If you are using Ubuntu this  would be handy for the installation part"]},
{"question": "Hi everyone, i'm a 15 year old gamedev. I just released my first 3d game, so if you could check it out that would mean a lot :)", "details": "", "answers": ["While I haven\u2019t downloaded it, I just wanted to say good for you. The best programmers/game developers are those that are self-motivated and create their own stuff. I encourage you to continue to do so."]},
{"question": "Visual Studio Code November 2020", "details": "", "answers": ["I do wish they worked on performance instead of features. The last few months I've noticed my language extensions getting slower and slower. At first I thought it was the extensions, but it seems to be related to how vs code handles larger files. Less than 5k lines, but because of the architecture, I cannot split it up."]},
{"question": "Hello. The question is: write a flowchart that prints all prime numbers up to n. And the link below is the answer. But I don't actually understand what the fuck is going on with \"k\" and \"a\". Please help me I would appreciate it", "details": "", "answers": ["k appears to be counting the number of primes found, and is used as the index into array a[ ] to store the primes for printing when N is reached.That's one crappy flowchart."]},
{"question": "The version 5.6.1 of KDevelop, the powerful KDE IDE was released", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to work with Pandas in Python", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to burn $72K testing Firebase + Cloud Run and almost go bankrupt", "details": "", "answers": ["I\u2019ve seen similar posts before and I feel like the takeaway is not to use firebase. From what I understand, it\u2019s not too expensive for little things but it\u2019s really easy to cause the cost to explode."]},
{"question": "Virtual Events Suck", "details": "", "answers": ["For me personally the only benefit with going to an event in person over watching some recordings afterwards is that it's much easier for me to focus if I go there. If I watch the stuff from office I will be distracted by ordinary work things. Going to some conference center in some other city pretty much solved that for me.But now? Now I have no idea why I would participate in some online event like this. I don't think I understand the offering any more. Someone here who have participated in these things and can share what the point is?"]},
{"question": "Does anyone understand any of this assembly code?", "details": "", "answers": ["That's not assembly code.  You're looking at a bunch of random looking english text in a disassembler."]},
{"question": "Docker and AWS Elastic Container Service from a User Perspective", "details": "", "answers": ["Hi all,I recently put together a video highlighting ECS and how it works from the user perspective. I go over a bunch of the concepts and walk you through how folks would typically use ECS.Given ECS and Containers in general are really gaining momentum these days I figured this could be a helpful video for some.Any feedback appreciated."]},
{"question": "Creating layered architectures in the workflow style", "details": "", "answers": ["One way to do this in the object-oriented/REST style (...)I think that you are conflating OOP with \"Class as entity only\" approach. OOP was conceived with objects being '(...) individual computers on a network, only able to communicate with messages' and not as a entities/aggregate roots. Nothing in OOP states that objects should not orchestrate other objects or they should represent business entity. I'd suggest a change here - what you are describing is a particular approach to OOP design that, taken to the extreme, produces badly designed systems.Overall, quite a nice and informative description of a particular solution, but... It's not really a different perspective. It's THE solution(s) when you want to orchestrate things (edit) in context of what you've described(/edit)."]},
{"question": "Pretty interesting video", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Cybersecurity resources from around the web", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Docker Desktop 3.0.0: Smaller, Faster Releases", "details": "", "answers": ["But waiting for docker to download a half gig plus update on slow office internet was excellent thinking time..."]},
{"question": "What are the uses of JavaScript", "details": "", "answers": ["What kind of question is that?"]},
{"question": "Scaling Cache Infrastructure at Pinterest", "details": "", "answers": ["Can you downscale your google spam infrastructure?"]},
{"question": "Chrome is Bad", "details": "", "answers": ["This might be useful advice if I were on a Mac and running Chrome... but as far as \"programming\" goes it has no details, which I'm sure would make an interesting read!What exactly is Chrome doing that causes slowness when it's not open? And is it doing something wrong, or is there a performance bug in WindowServer? Does this issue also happen in other operating systems? If not, what's different between WindowServer from other window rendering systems / Chrome on Mac from Chrome on other operating systems?"]},
{"question": "Can anyone give me any suggestions or links to good resources for using functions? Had a high level overview on Thursday's class on this with a final project due a few days later.. hardly shown how to go about it at all. Any help is appreciated!", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "I Made Among Us In Scratch... (cursed)", "details": "", "answers": ["WD. Scratch isn't easy to use and you really pushed it to its limits.Keep the passion up! You should cross post in  Us!"]},
{"question": "Zodiac '340 Cipher' cracked by code experts 51 years after it was sent to the S.F. Chronicle", "details": "", "answers": [""]},
{"question": "Two Programmers and Mathematician Crack Zodiac Killer's cipher 50 yrs later", "details": "", "answers": ["I HOPE YOU ARE HAVING LOTS OF FUN IN TRYING TO CATCH ME THAT WASNT ME ON THE TV SHOW WHICH BRINGS UP A POINT ABOUT ME I AM NOT AFRAID OF THE GAS CHAMBER BECAUSE IT WILL SEND ME TO PARADICE ALL THE SOONER BECAUSE I NOW HAVE ENOUGH SLAVES TO WORK FOR ME WHERE EVERYONE ELSE HAS NOTHING WHEN THEY REACH PARADICE SO THEY ARE AFRAID OF DEATH I AM NOT AFRAID BECAUSE I KNOW THAT MY NEW LIFE ISLIFE WILL BE AN EASY ONE IN PARADICE DEATH"]},
{"question": "Advent of Code 2020 - Day 8", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Tiny ~/.emacs for beginners to Common Lisp programming with line-by-line explanation", "details": "", "answers": ["Nice. I remember when I took the plunge into configuring Emacs with Evil mode. Since then I use Doom Emacs. Was a fun learning exercise."]},
{"question": "Method Chaining is Awesome", "details": "", "answers": ["Initially, I only hated it because in most editors, the auto indentation of the next line that isn't part of the chain wants to go to the chain level. Eventually I settled on formatting it likeobject\n    .chain()\n    .these()\n    .methods()\n;\n"]},
{"question": "Hi everyone, i'm a gamedev. I also do youtube. My goal is to reach 5 subscribers by the end of the day, so if you enjoy the content you can subscribe cause that helps me a lot :)", "details": "", "answers": ["Would check out but yt is down ;)"]},
{"question": "Im a noob at programming, Using loops how can I program the pattern in this link? :>", "details": "", "answers": ["What have you tried so far? What does it produce?"]},
{"question": "Please Help! Is the behaviour shown in the video normal for vscode?", "details": "", "answers": ["Yea"]},
{"question": "Metaprogramming", "details": "", "answers": ["This has chosen interesting definitions for metaprogramming (neither the main one nor the \"this is an alternative definition that this course doesn't cover\" are what I've typically come to understand as metaprogramming)I've always heard metaprogramming to mean \"code that writes more (source) code\", e.g. JSON -> Java object deserialization or the ORM that \"automatically\" converts a table row to an application level objectMaybe I'm out of touch lol"]},
{"question": "What Programming Language You Should Learn First?", "details": "", "answers": ["That is true, but likely not helpful to people actually asking the question."]},
{"question": "pipx \u2014 Install and Run Python Applications in Isolated Environments", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How I Learned to Code and Built a Real Software Product in 6 Months", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Chain python commands with Unix-like pipes to use in the command line", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "The Piet-GPU vision", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Serverless cron twitter bot", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "A dirty hack to ease the usage of Log4J2 in Spring Boot", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "For all those wanting to learn full stack development with c# at no charge.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Programming Languages for Hacking", "details": "", "answers": ["Holy hell is this a god awful article or what? Written by someone that really has no idea.C is an ancient programming language of the world.Not to even mention that things start numbered, then have none, then are numbered again.SQLIt is one of the favorite programming languages for hacking.Just wow.Likewise, the C programming language, C++ is also the leading programming language for hacking.There's two leading languages? Wow."]},
{"question": "Reasons You Shouldn't Invest in Development with Angular and Why", "details": "", "answers": ["Holy  Batman."]},
{"question": "Best budget smartphones to buy in 2020", "details": "", "answers": ["Only a few days left of 2020; what should I buy in 2021?"]},
{"question": "TN-SD-01: Enabling SD/uSD Card Lock/Unlock in Linux", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Learn how the \"sliding window\" algorithm works step by step: Longest substring without duplicate characters", "details": "", "answers": ["I'll repeat my earlier comment on an earlier post of yours with a similar video:How does watching someone click  Run a bunch of times make this \"easy to understand\"? There's no narrative, the time between clicks is sometimes too short to process what just happened before the next thing already happens and sometimes too long to make you go  The code shown has no real use (it would've been MUCH better if it had an arrow showing which line is currently being executed). Etc. etc.No, sorry, this is not \"easy to understand\",  if you're unfamiliar with  Sliding Window and are trying to understand it. 0/10 would recommend."]},
{"question": "Auto generating SEO-friendly URLs with Scrapy pipelines", "details": "", "answers": ["if it works like you say, great work.  i\u2019m going to try it. possible improvement: can you supply a pytest example, a simple github repo or gist?"]},
{"question": "How can I scrape 5-7 years of Twitter data using an API like tweepy.", "details": "", "answers": ["Twitter API has a limit of how many tweets you can get at a time. 3200 tweets last I checked. It\u2019s a really hot database so going 7 years in time is not a very good easy thing to do especially for your use case"]},
{"question": "Taking advantage of Python's concurrent futures to full saturate your bandwidth", "details": "", "answers": ["You are using the ThreadPoolExecutor for exactly the right job, so don\u2019t let them down you on this one. Any read() or write() will release the GIL, so the code runs concurrently while inside C code. You can even compute hashes concurrently, because hashlib also releases the GIL.So important thing: If the majority of time is spent in C code calls or sleeping/blocked, a ThreadPoolExecutor is fine. Otherwise a ProcessPoolExecutor is required. But then, optimize for sending larger jobs to the pool, as individual python instances have to be created. These communicate via pickle, so the parameters and return values have to be serializable. ProcessPoolExecutor can not share things like OpenCL contexts and similar.\u200bCode feedback:with concurrent.futures.ThreadPoolExecutor(processes) as pool:\n    list(pool.map(download, df[\"url\"]))\nThis is sub-optimal. Imagine an embedded system, like a Raspberry Pi with 1GB ram and a huge HDD. Task the Pi to download 10 TB of data from a million URLs.You create a list of possibly millions of status codes or worse a list with millions of None values, just to drive the map.Better use a for loop to drive the map:with concurrent.futures.ThreadPoolExecutor(processes) as pool:\n    for _ in pool.map(download, df[\"url\"]):\n        pass\nThis exhausts the map operation while not keeping anything unnecessary in memory.\u200bAnother thing: look at the default value for the number of threads created by the ThreadPoolExecutor. Think about what happens if you run it on a 64 core+SMT dual-socket server. Do you want to create 512 parallel download threads? This will probably earn you a ban by the CDN or API for an attempted DOS attack.Quoting :Changed in version 3.8: Default value of max_workers is changed to\nmin(32, os.cpu_count() + 4). This default value preserves at least 5\nworkers for I/O bound tasks. It utilizes at most 32 CPU cores for CPU\nbound tasks which release the GIL. And it avoids using very large\nresources implicitly on many-core machines.\nIf you want to keep it as-is, verify that multiprocessing.cpu_count() never returns None. os.cpu_count() may return None.Better leave it at the default, unless you know that you need at least or at most X workers."]},
{"question": "How to Implement Bill Gates\u2019 Favorite Pancake Sorting Algorithm Using Python Programming Language", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Flutter vs React Native: Best for Cross-Platform Development", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Modeling programming method's impact | First published post, so feedback very welcome", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Please give your feedback; I found this site for my programming queries", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Design Patterns in Python - good reference for solving software problems", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "19 Tips to Prepare for a Virtual Interview", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "React Hooks Tutorial \u2014 Create a Number Trivia Generator Website", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "The Fastest Way to Compute the Fibonacci Sequence", "details": "", "answers": ["I think they're some pretty cool optimizations in this article, but it's misleading to compare this to the fast doubling method. This optimized algorithm only produces an approximation of fibonacci(n) (we can't get infinite precision out of our floats) while the fast doubling method is numerically precise."]},
{"question": "It's Time to Embrace Kubernetes! Really? (Part 1+2)", "details": "", "answers": ["Part 2 is here: I thought it was pretty well balanced in terms of how to figure out if you should, or shouldn't."]},
{"question": "My little HTML-based fullscreen clock", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Understanding React Rendering", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Build a Docker Image for your application from Dockerfile | My Attempt to explain", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Microsoft: Turning Excel into a Turing-complete programming language", "details": "", "answers": ["The boss' cost example was funny. But I had the opposite situation. My girlfriend's company had a bunch of people running customer orders through Excel programs. They had to set up sheets with deals/etc manually and then wait up to hours for a few hundred thousands orders to be calculated in their massive slow Excel app that used \"find row/column\" operations rather than binary search to search through data tables. So I made the same program in C# (not in an afternoon, a bit more time...) but then it could run each order Excel sheet in less than a second, dealing with all the deals etc automatically rather than manually.So Excel may give you a quick cheap prototype, but running your company on that for years? Yeah not the best cost efficiency"]},
{"question": "GUIDE: Consuming an API in Linx (low-code)", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "\u201cA damn stupid thing to do\u201d\u2014the origins of C", "details": "", "answers": ["Goes all the way back to the 1950s. Interesting."]},
{"question": "The Code Will Never Judge You \u2013 Letters To A New Developer", "details": "", "answers": ["...but the compiler, now that's one judgemental bitch."]},
{"question": "Project Reunion 0.1 Prerelease", "details": "", "answers": ["I lost count of how many Windows API sets there are now"]},
{"question": "Webscraping with Python using BeautifulSoup", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Learn how the \"sliding window\" algorithm works step by step: Longest substring without duplicate characters", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Building GraphQL API with NestJS", "details": "", "answers": ["Is this like Apollo GraphQL?"]},
{"question": "Data Science career worth it?", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "New Hacker Rank 30 days of Code", "details": "", "answers": ["This was interesting"]},
{"question": "cebsocket: Lightweight WebSocket library for C", "details": "", "answers": ["Nice. I'd suggest adding void *user_data; to the client struct, as it's a standard way to allow the callbacks to access the required application state."]},
{"question": "CSS Variables and How To Use Them", "details": "", "answers": ["A lot of the latest CSS features feel like they came along a little too late and now I'm still using old tricks to accomplish similar things as flex and variables would.I wish the article also touched on variables with shadow roots and gave more examples for how :root works with vars.It would be neat to also see how this approach could be used to improve maintainability for certain problems."]},
{"question": "A Dead-Simple Userspace Read-Copy-Update implementation: What do you think of this proof of concept? Any advise?", "details": "", "answers": ["To clarify: I am the author of this repo, and I would like to know what do you think about this concept, and this implementation.DSURCU is a proof of concept for a Dead-Simple Userspace Read-Copy-Update. The main goal is to play with the concept and to show it is possible to implement RCU in userspace in a really simple way.This is a pet project of mine that I think could interest some of you.\nAny feedbacks would be appreciated. ;)"]},
{"question": "Get all social media information about a person", "details": "", "answers": ["Sure, I'll clone this random repository and type my LinkedIn/Instagram password into it. What could go wrong?"]},
{"question": "Why software ends up complex \u00b7 Alex Gaynor", "details": "", "answers": ["Short article.I think the biggest thing when it comes to \"preserving the conceptual integrity\" of software, is you need a strong architect to accept and reject ideas, and that comes from a strong architect thinking about the problem deeply and creating the abstractions correctly."]},
{"question": "Advent of Code 2020 - Day 9", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "If-then-else had to be invented", "details": "", "answers": ["If you want to talk about keywords, I think static takes the prize."]},
{"question": "An overview of end-to-end entity resolution for big data", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Alda and the nREPL protocol", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Liquid Warping GAN - \"Deepfake\" Movements with 1 image ONLY", "details": "", "answers": ["Every time I see something like this I wonder.. why isn't it looking more realistic? The main reason why this question pops in my head is .  Would it be all that difficult to model the human body movements into a morphable model (like they did for the face) that excludes anatomically incorrect outputs?"]},
{"question": "How not to ask for a job", "details": "", "answers": ["I'd just have responded generically to the first email.\"Thank you for your interest but at this time we are not in need of QA specialists.\"And just ignore future emails."]},
{"question": "Essential guide to SEO for web developers", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Taking advantage of Python\u2019s concurrent futures to full saturate your bandwidth", "details": "", "answers": ["I think it would probably be better to use a wget or curl subprocess, outputting to a known filename. On a posix system at least, that should actually have less overhead than a thread (no shared memory state). As much as I like python, it\u2019s not exactly a tool for maximum performance, and I\u2019ve never managed to saturate more than a 40Gbps connection using python (There are currently 800Gbps cards in existence) with anything other than random data."]},
{"question": "Operating System Dev Tutorial series - For anyone interested, i've been working on this series for the past few months", "details": "", "answers": ["Finally more OS Dev stuff! Quite a lack of it to be honest."]},
{"question": "Automatic Jira Task Estimation based on the Azure Machine Learning Predictive Model", "details": "", "answers": ["We spend 2 hours twice a month estimating the backlog tasks. For a team of 5 people that is 10 hours, and on a monthly basis 20 hours of planning. It\u2019s quite a lot, given that the programmer, hopefully, earns on average 30 USD per hour. Annually it means 8 thousands USD spent on planning alone. In this case, 4 additional people from different departments take part in the planning as they are responsible for the whole process of delivering the software to the client.You sir, are too optimistic."]},
{"question": "C++ json libs - nlohmann and RapidJSON", "details": "", "answers": ["nlohmann_json is surprisingly compatible with C++. I haven't used RapidJSON."]},
{"question": "Celebrating the centenary of Dr. Kenneth Iverson and looking to the future of Iverson Notation", "details": "", "answers": ["On Thursday, December 17th, at 2 pm EDT, there will be an online event to celebrate the 100th birthday of Ken Iverson and to discuss the future of \"Iverson Notation\" which underlies languages like APL, J, k, and q.  You can sign up here: These languages offer powerful alternatives to the dominant paradigm of C-like languages by incorporating a few simple data types with arrays, functions, and higher-level functions as first-class citizens.  They use symbolic notation to leverage our ability to reason about computation and algorithms.This might be exemplified by comparing two versions of a simple expression: \"1+1\" versus \"one plus one\".  Which of the two is clearer?  We would argue that it is the former but only if you understand the meaning of weird symbols like \"1\" and \"+\"."]},
{"question": "Blockchain is not like the early days of the Internet", "details": "", "answers": ["Innovation is increasing around blockchain, particularly with enterprise private blockchain. Innovation in the  of applied blockchain that is a monumental waste of time. Yay.Private blockchains are pointless. It was literally invented to solve a problem with a public facing currency. And people want to use it to solve something completely different and nothing comes of it. I'm shocked."]},
{"question": "Guessing a Number with Genetic Algorithm using Julia", "details": "", "answers": ["That is the longest explaination I have ever seen for a loss function. Also, abs should be  your loss function. Number and value are bad names for variables. Oh its this guy again."]},
{"question": "Data With R Programming", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Sockets in shell", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to start your domain driven project?", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Best Time to Buy and Sell Stock I and II - Leetcode", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Kubuntu Focus M2 Linux laptop review and MacBook Pro comparison", "details": "", "answers": ["Is every non mac laptop have trackpad shifted to left? Why?"]},
{"question": "CSS Individual Transform Properties", "details": "", "answers": ["How is order of operations habdled with these? transform functions are order dependent; the following rules have different results:\ntransform: translate(100, 0) rotate(90deg);\nvs.\ntransform: rotate(90) translate (100, 0);\nBefore, if there was a conflict in rules, the rule wirth higher specificity would win (as expected). If both rules had the same specificity, then the rule ordered last in the document wins. This can be surprising and hard to predict in modern toolchains, but is consistent for all other CSS rules.With this proposal, order and precedence of these rules becomes a lot more important, and I don\u2019t think any other rule acts this way, as everything else I can think of (border, padding, position, etc) can be applied in any order in the \u201ccascading\u201c hierarchy."]},
{"question": "SaaS Development Company: Leverage Our Know - How Build Great SaaS Product", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "About Cyberpunk 2077 and AMD CPUs - Silent's Blog", "details": "", "answers": ["So I'm not a game developer, so I don't know how much this applies for game systems, but in large backend services I've worked on we mostly initialise the size of our CPU-bound threadpools using std::thread::hardware_concurrency and it usually works fine: Is there a reason why video games don't use this  ? Granted our hardware platforms are relatively homogeneous compared to consumer machines but I would feel like this is sufficiently portable to be reasonable."]},
{"question": "Back-End payment processing integration for the iGaming industry in c#", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Hexpalette - A fast color schemes generator for developers, designers.", "details": "", "answers": ["For some unfathomable reason, color scheme generators now need a sign in and sign up button along with a privacy policy and legal notice."]},
{"question": "SonarQube, SonarCloud users have the tooling to own Code Security", "details": "", "answers": ["Old-school SAST tools aren't built for developers. They cast a very broad net, raising an issue for everything even remotely suspicious, and make an auditor sort it out. At SonarSource, we know developers don't have time for that.This is the maker of Sonarqube, right? The tool that brought me such fine warnings as \"switch statements should have at least 3 cases\" and \"labels should be all capital letters\""]},
{"question": "I published this article \u201cThe complete beginners\u2019s guide to web scraping\u201d. Would love your feedback on how to improve :)", "details": "", "answers": ["Nice effort."]},
{"question": "Estimator.dev \u2013 the modern JavaScript savings calculator", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Test Driven Development with JUnit 5. Part 4", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Understanding event loop in JavaScript", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Minimal safe Bash script template", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Read a paper: GiantVM\u2014a type-II hypervisor implementing many-to-one virtualization", "details": "", "answers": ["Hmm, the lack of fault tolerance sounds like the achilles heel of this. By putting many physical machines into a huge VM, you increase the possibility of failure by a lot.They argue that applications should handle this by being tolerant to faults of the underlying hardware, but to me, the major way in which applications are doing this is scaling out. But the entire selling point of the paper is that scaling out is too hard for applications."]},
{"question": "Unwinding a Bug - How C++ Exceptions Work", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "50 free tools and resources you're gonna love", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "An app ditched Firebase to use Booster in production", "details": "", "answers": ["\"Why we ditched product X\" articles/videos are an important antidote to kool-aid fueled tech frenzies."]},
{"question": "[Self Promotion] Earn your share of $25,000 wrangling US presidential election data", "details": "", "answers": ["Hi ,CEO of DoltHub () here. We are running a contest on DoltHub to gather and clean US Presidential Election precinct-level results. The prize pool is $25,000. The prize will be divided up in February based on number of cells added to the database, last edit of a single cell wins.This kind of contest is possible because Dolt () is a database with Git-style version control. It's the only SQL database you can branch and merge allowing hundreds of people to collaboratively edit.For more information and some hints about how to get started, check out:We're looking forward to this community's contributions."]},
{"question": "Essential Skills Every Software Developer Should Have", "details": "", "answers": ["Git is one of the most basic skills a developer needs. Even basic tasks like writing good commit messages and separating changes into different commits seems like a challenge to most, not to even mention interactive rebase."]},
{"question": "JesseAI - Jealousy \"DATABASE\" - 2020/12/15", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Coordinated disclosure of XML round-trip vulnerabilities in Go XML", "details": "", "answers": ["Mattermost: encoding/xml is seriously vulnerable to privilege escalation attacksGo: we can't fix it, and we'll mark it as 'unfixable' so people stop bothering us with this"]},
{"question": "Create memes with Python", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "You are an Enterprise company (Bank, Telco, etc). You develop an app in Java, Python, Node or Ruby. Your app dependencies (jars, pip, npm modules, gems) come from...", "details": "", "answers": ["How many internal \u201ccurated\u201d registries are actually curated? All I\u2019ve seen are just proxies of public registries."]},
{"question": "7 javaecript useful array methods", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Why We Switched from bcc-tools to libbpf-tools for BPF Performance Analysis", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Hacker Rank 30 Days of Code | Operators and Conditional Statements | C ++ | Let's Code! |", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Here are some great insight tips on how to build a great engineering culture that attracts engineers", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Walking the Path to Cleaner Code", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to build a great organization: Software Engineer\u2019s Perspective", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Apache Beam: A Basic Guide", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Data Economy Challenge: more than 65,000 USD in prizes!", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Why you shouldn't rely on developer metrics", "details": "", "answers": ["I feel like it's worth mentioning Goodhart's law here:When a measure becomes a target, it ceases to be a good measure"]},
{"question": "How to implement a custom event service in JS", "details": "", "answers": ["Events are under-rated as a feature and can save you from some hairy refactors."]},
{"question": "SwiftUI tutorials rewritten completely", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Scheduling All Kinds of Recurring Jobs with Python", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Command injection: how it works, what are the risks, and how to prevent it", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "HTML Space Code", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Setting Up and Running Apache Kafka on Windows OS", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "This is valid C code. I'm not happy about it.", "details": "", "answers": ["I've compiled it so you don't have to:   ```\n     $./a.out    69\n```"]},
{"question": "Building A Fantasy Game Console Emulator: System Overview and Graphics Pipeline", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "This is what we think is the number one information technology related problem", "details": "", "answers": ["Get this click bait bullshit outta here. The author claims that the largest problem is that you cannot transfer services without your data following you. Then states \u201cit\u2019s amazing this is a problem at all\u201dBut it isn\u2019t amazing. Bodies have attempted to standardize data transfer and holding. Guess what happened?But never mind that, imagine trying to build a new product and being handcuffed by regulatory bodies standardizing all your possible data to be capable of sharing, and having your data leaking IP details. This would be a software incubation disaster. We\u2019d still be barely scratching the web under this idea.Oh and look at that. The bottom is an advertising for their standard that\u2019s definitely totally going to achieve imploding data handling, turn it to an utter IP shit show, and definitely not be relegated to the horrifying bullshit of days long past. Fuck EDI.Edit:It\u2019s an advertisement for a blockchain. This is all sorts of batshit yikes beyond even what my post imagined. Lol."]},
{"question": "Study Buddy - MicroPython micro:bit Educational App", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "I made a list of the best articles, talks, videos and tutorials to learn GO!", "details": "", "answers": ["Hey fellow Programmers :)I am a huge fan of the Go programming language because of its simple and pragmatic nature. However, as Go is not as popular as for example Python, it is sometimes a little bit harder to find great learning materials for it on the internet...So I made this little side project, Golang Resources, where I curated the best learning materials for Go.I hope this is helpful to you!Mike"]},
{"question": "UI design in visual studio Blend", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "The Best Ruby Blogs", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Welcome Yari: MDN Web Docs has a new platform", "details": "", "answers": ["I love MDN so it\u2019s great to see they\u2019re making it easier for contributions and community maintenance by moving to GitHub and support for Markdown"]},
{"question": "JavaScript to Know for React", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "FREE Reverse Engineering Course", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to Fetch a Remote Branch using Git", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Pointers Are Complicated II, or: We need better language specs", "details": "", "answers": ["Why does the author claim that UB code is \"unreachable\" by definition?  Just because the code has undefined behavior doesn't mean it can't be reached."]},
{"question": "Ethical Programming - Is It Worth It?", "details": "", "answers": ["I don't think programming is any different from any other area of life in this regard - your ethical approach to it will depend on who you are as a person. You either care, or you don't."]},
{"question": "Oblivious DNS Over HTTPS", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to Use Page Object Model in Selenium", "details": "", "answers": ["I remember I tried writing tests in Selenium in the past. Writing them was very hard for me, felt like im missing something, and the same test could fail or pass randomly. This article was a good read and gave me a new perspective on selenium"]},
{"question": "Global Network Encryption Investment Security Service (GNEISS.io)", "details": "", "answers": ["World's first P2P decentralized free market blockchain platform! GNEISS makes blockchain technology easy by offering the first intuitive P2P free market blockchain platform in the world! Create, transfer, or trade any digital asset or smart contract. GNEISS, reinventing the financial wheel.Feel free to comment on GNEISS and let us know what you think or if you have any questions! We should be out of beta in a few months and currently have the most advanced blockchain platform tech in the whole world!"]},
{"question": "What it's like being a Web Developer \ud83d\udc68\u200d\ud83d\udcbb", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "[RFC] Preemptive Error Checking \u00b7 Issue #81 \u00b7 chaos-lang/chaos", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Understanding How to Use Klibs in the Nanos Unikernel", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Deploy a Free Website With Jekyll and GitHub Pages", "details": "", "answers": ["Personally, I use  which is also very good."]},
{"question": "Google suite is in the middle of an outage", "details": "", "answers": ["I really hope they share an incident report for this one, I'm very interested to see what could cause such a wide reaching outage"]},
{"question": "Instagram's Million Dollar Bug (2015)", "details": "", "answers": ["Asshole move on FB's part. Also it does not seem like a good idea to me to mistreat the person who just got all up in your shit. Next time he discovers one of those security vulnerabilities he may be more inclined to publicize it to some shady people instead of trying to get you guys to pay up."]},
{"question": "Uses of Java", "details": "", "answers": ["What  are  the main  uses of  java in  the world "]},
{"question": "How To Build A Drowsiness Detector Using Machine Learning", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Microsoft Open-Sources Fluid Framework for Distributed, Scalable, Real-Time Collaborative Web Apps", "details": "", "answers": ["I guess this is how vs code works when they do collaborative work? \u200bAnyway it's always nice to open source stuff!"]},
{"question": "The cleverest floppy disc protection ever? Western Security Ltd", "details": "", "answers": ["There was another one called, IIRC, pro-lock. They used a laser to burn a hole in a specific place on the disk, and the program would try to format that track and it would only work if the format failed. Which meant you had to leave your one and only master disk not-write-protected."]},
{"question": "Silent Night Performed by Blob Opera", "details": "", "answers": ["This is beautiful \ud83d\ude22"]},
{"question": "most graduates unable to pass coding interviews", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Raft does not Guarantee Liveness in the face of Network Faults", "details": "", "answers": ["My understanding was that this was proved generally, that safe distributed consensus cannot guarantee liveness."]},
{"question": "My Java Space Invaders Game", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "[Tutorial] Build voice/video calling into your android application", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Statistical Approaches for Performance Analysis", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Retro Programming is Fun!", "details": "", "answers": ["Hope you have fun with this. I have fond memories of .You also might want to check out the Forth programming language. It's incredibly small and easy to bootstrap on a 6502-sized microprocessor, but is still pretty powerful, easier than assembly, but you're still working pretty close to the metal, without a whole bunch of layers of abstraction."]},
{"question": "Creating open source software is a delight", "details": "", "answers": ["If you know how. I still barely can make a rng for dice rolls."]},
{"question": "Build A Twitter Bot Using NodeJS", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Goodbye, JavaScript: Formality is now implemented in itself and released as a Haskell project and library!", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Tips and Tricks for Writing Linux BPF Applications with libbpf", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "git wip: What the heck was I just doing?", "details": "", "answers": ["That's actually a nice idea, thanks"]},
{"question": "Most useful Javascript tools for Animation", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "The case of the extra 40ms", "details": "", "answers": ["Integrating software with 3rd party hardware and 3rd party software, with a 3rd party integrator in the mix is a deep circle of hell.  These kinds of projects tend to include a whole pile of empowered non-technicals involved, all with a mentality that goes something like \"How come you guys can't get this shit to just work?\"\u00a0The worst part?  Everyone acts surprised when their next business-synergistic--idea that involves ridiculous piles of integration detective work goes to hell in a handbasket....."]},
{"question": "Adding BPF target support to the Rust compiler", "details": "", "answers": ["In case it helps anyone else, ."]},
{"question": "Hey Guys i\u2019m streaming daily on my twitch channel! Please follow me! I\u2019m not a Pro! I\u2019m just getting started and I will improve my skills live! We will have long different conversations and trust me it will be interesting.", "details": "", "answers": ["No I don't think so"]},
{"question": "NodeJS Server using Core HTTP Module", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Leading platform to recruit developers is promoting drug usage still can't believing what I'm seeing here xD", "details": "", "answers": ["Honeypot: "]},
{"question": "Every single google service is currently out, including their cloud console. Let's take a moment to feel the pain of their devops team", "details": "", "answers": ["wow, according to the status dashboard:\n\n\n\nthis will be remembered as the great outage"]},
{"question": "The 4 most hated programming languages: Experts pile on Javascript, C++, and more", "details": "", "answers": ["C++ is a cobbled-together monstrosity. The use of iterators over STL containers is most disgusting. The ceremony and verbosity is outlandish.The requirement of including templates in your compiled source is widely regarded as a part of C++ that is just  broken."]},
{"question": "Write a program in javascript to find whether the number entered by the user is prime or not.", "details": "", "answers": ["This solution works but as the number gets large it becomes more and more inefficient if the number is prime. This is because you divide the number by every number below itself up to and including n-1. The largest number that you actually need to check up to is the square root of n (rounded down to the nearest integer). This can be found using Math.sqrt(n)."]},
{"question": "How to Develop On Demand eLearning Website Using Angular?", "details": "", "answers": ["Step 1: Don't use Angular."]},
{"question": "SolarWinds Hack Could Affect 18K Customers", "details": "", "answers": ["And one of them is the Dominion voting machine that was rigged in the elections. Yay!"]},
{"question": "26 Great Tools & Websites Every Developer Should Know", "details": "", "answers": ["Several tools of possible interest and NOT A SINGLE LINK!"]},
{"question": "Python For Data Science", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Ethical Programming \u2014 Is It Worth It?", "details": "", "answers": ["Right...you submitted the same story, posted to Pragmatic Pineapple instead of Medium, ."]},
{"question": "Promises in Javascript", "details": "", "answers": ["From the second paragraph:Now here come the promises. Promises allow you to write asynchronous code so the promises can  and they will resolve and give us the value whenever they are finished (Emphasis mine.)This is fundamentally wrong. Promises defer the execution of a function until later in the stack, but it's all run in the same 'thread'. A long-running operation in a promise will still block the main thread and UI. Javascript is synchronous and single-threaded until you get  involved.Here's an example you can run in your own browser:const heavyOp = () => {\n  for(let i = 0; i < 1000000; i ++){\n    for(let j = 0; j < 1000000; j ++){\n      for(let k = 0; k < 1000000; k ++){\n        1 + 1;\n      }\n    }\n  }\n}\n\nconsole.log('Start');\nnew Promise((res)=>{\n  console.log('Start big work');\n  heavyOp();\n  console.log('End big work');\n  res();\n})\n\n// This will never run if the Promise is put on the stack first\nfor(let q = 0; q < 5; q++){\n  console.log('Counting... ' + q);\n}\nconsole.log('End');\nBecause heavyOp runs on the main thread, you'll never get to End. Depending on your browser you  make it to the Counting... section, but in my tests with FF and Chrome, they both executed the promise first."]},
{"question": "Scripting transmission to download selected files from 625 torrents.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Live Hacking Session Part 2", "details": "", "answers": ["Check out this live hacking session from GOTOpia Europe as Scott Helme exposes the flaws of an application using SQL injection, the most common form of attack that we see online, based on the #OWASP top 10."]},
{"question": "Beginning Ethical Hacking with Kali Linux: Computational Techniques for Resolving Security Issues", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Mikado Refactoring with C++ Feature Macros", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "I wrote a visualizer (my first!) in C and legacy OpenGL", "details": "", "answers": ["I originally wrote this code because I wanted a visualizer/video to use for a song I wrote.I upload all of the music I write to my youtube channel, and I always try to find something fun or fitting for the video that goes with it.  I decided this time to tack a stab at writing my own \"visualizer\" specifically for this song!  I'm comfortable in C, but had never really used OpenGL directly so this was my first time doing that and it was really fun!Some notes:"]},
{"question": "A super underrated talk about makepad.dev, a completely custom, high-performance UI/layout/IDE project built with WebGL", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Vercel has secured $40M in series B funding", "details": "", "answers": ["Congrats to them. Their free tier has been so generous."]},
{"question": "Streaming React Development", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Add iOS14 Widget Support to Your Cordova Apps", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Hacker Rank 30 Days of Code | Day 4,5 | Class, and Instance and Loops | C ++ | Let's Code! |", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Microsoft Click Once no longer working. ( I am not the original poster just have the same issue).", "details": "", "answers": ["If you are running click once dont update. there are also several issues with the new wizard (FTp no longer seems supported, and alot of options are grayed out)"]},
{"question": "Rt.cpan.org will sunset on March first, 2021", "details": "", "answers": ["This is not good. Why?In many ways it is for the perl folks to admit deadness. \"We don't need this feature anymore\nbecause xyz offers it already.\"Extend it to perl and it will go \"we don't need perl anymore because xyz offers this already\nin a better way\".If you are facing extinction then you need to do more to avoid it, rather than help accelerate\nit by removing reasons for people to use a language. And if you think \"but cpan is not \nrelevant anymore because of github\" then you entered into PRECISELY the mindset\nthat obsoletes perl out of the pool as-is. It's the fallacy of the \"seemingly logical\" attempt\nto reason about obsoletion - the march into total extinction. (Some perl guys still refuse\nto accept that this is going on; it is literal dinosaur-fossification going on there. You just\ndon't want to accept the reality.)"]},
{"question": "Coordinated disclosure of XML round-trip vulnerabilities in Go XML", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Thanks to the Rasberry Pi in this Split Flap and a dash of Python, we were able to program it to run the classic Snake Game.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "And now for \u2026 Firefox 84", "details": "", "answers": ["resources loaded from  are  to have been delivered ly (see Secure contexts), and also will not be treated as mixed content.Finally a little vindication for my plan to invest in local web UIs as a compromise between my background as a desktop programmer and the fact that web browsers are clearly the best-funded 'desktop' GUI around. (Since Qt is stuck with C++, Flutter requires Dart, and desktop GUIs have generally seen little interest since 2010ish)"]},
{"question": "\ud83c\udf99 Trae Robrock: Understanding Your Risk Tolerance As An Engineer | Maintainable", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How FreeSO (The Sims Online) created a 3D mode out of 2D sprites from the original The Sims", "details": "", "answers": ["Interesting. So the original Sims sprites were 2d sprites.. but had 3d depth information in them as well... so it was possible to reconstruct the 3d models from them using that.Would be interesting to have a list of games that also stored depth information in their 2d sprites, as those would also be good candidates for 3d conversion."]},
{"question": "SuperRT chip by Ben Carter -- raytracing on SNES", "details": "", "answers": ["\"so this isn't the case where there's a PC or an ARM SoC running everything behind the scenes. The SNES is fairly in the driving seat here\""]},
{"question": "Bringing React's ideas to server-rendered Rails views", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Free Ethical Hacking Books", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Your Go-To-Guide to Holiday Entertainment: The Best Books, T.V. Shows, and Movies For Programmers", "details": "", "answers": ["Lol wtf"]},
{"question": "API - The HTTP Status Codes Problem", "details": "", "answers": ["Strongly disagree. HTTP status code nomenclature does extensively describe virtually every situation which could happen with your HTTP request: wrong Accept-* headers value, Content-Length is absent, HTTP method is unsupported, URI too long, etc.What the RFC fails to describe is what to do with the error. As we discussed, errors could be resolvable or not.No, all of those errors are strictly unrecoverable, unless there is a human sitting at the other end.If the error is unresolvable, all this status codes and headers stuff is simply irrelevant to clients, even more so to interim proxies. In fact, three error codes are enough:404 to denote \u2018uncertainity\u2019 cases (the request could be repeated \u2014 possibly with different outcomes);Please do  do this.In a modern world we have to deal with a literal mess: HTTP status codes are used not for the protocol\u2019s purity sake, but to build the graphs; their semantic meaning forgotten;Really? If I return a 405 Method Not Allowed, the semantic meaning of \"you can't make a GET request to this endpoint\" is totally lost? I don't think so. 401 for lack of authentication headers and 411 for length required haven't had their meanings \"lost\" either - and those statuses will most likely be returned before your application code even starts executing, so there is no sense complaining about what statuses  web applications return."]},
{"question": "Pretty Logger 4 Java - now with themes support and more loggers", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Recursion in SQL Explained Visually", "details": "", "answers": ["The thing about recursion in SQL that makes it confusing is that IMO it's easier to think of it like iteration (though I know recursion and iteration are computationally equivalent)WITH RECURSIVE R(n) AS (\n    VALUES (1)\nUNION ALL\n    SELECT n+1 FROM R WHERE <foo>\n)\nSELECT sum(n) FROM R;\nIt's not super intuitive that R kind of represents a row definition in the first call, and will start as [n: 1], and that each iteration will have R be a single row, rather than a table/set which is more normal in a FROM clause.  The reason I say this is more like iteration is because it's a lot like this while loop:R = {n: 1}\nwhile <foo>\n    yield R\n    R = {n: R[n] + 1}\nRecursion might be more likedef R(n=1)\n    return if <foo>\n    yield n\n    R(n+1)\nBut you're not exactly invoking R as a function, and defining various arguments on it.  It's more like the i in a for loop or some state that gets modified in a while loop.That said, I've found that you often use RECURSIVE for similar reasons that I'd write a real recursive functions - namely when a table is representing a tree"]},
{"question": "Growing the .NET ecosystem", "details": "", "answers": ["Seems like the Dotnet team put a lot of thought into this and realized that if they want to commit to the open source path, they are going to have to give up control over the tools built around their framework. Also open source is a full time job, cant expect the community to suddenly start making great tools because you open sourced your code.  After reading this post, I wonder if the dotnet community would prefer if Microsoft would just maintain control of the tools?"]},
{"question": "Web Design Tips For Web Developers", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Python Programming For Data Science", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Timestamp is the right way to handle different timezone problem of date and time in database.", "details": "", "answers": ["Now, a user from Australia is posting a date and time for sales call on your website. Let say 12th December 2020 at 08:00 PM. You need to call that user at her provided time only. This datetime will be in Australian time zone. But your server will store it as it is and sales person will call her at USA 08:00 PM.To deal with this issue, Mysql timestamp is usedThis may not actually be the right solution if you're storing something like appointment times. Future times (i.e. appointments) should not be stored as a unix timestamp unless the time horizon is short enough that you can guarantee timezone rules will not change before then.Let's say you have an appointment for 9am on Dec 20th 2021 in Australia/Brisbane. It is not possible to define that moment as an absolute number of seconds from the Epoch, because you cannot know exactly when that moment will occur.This is because daylight savings rules might change between then and now, which means that the exact unix timestamp for 9am on Dec 20th 2021 is  until that moment has happened.This is why Java has the concept of ZonedDateTime, OffsetDateTime, LocalDateTime, and Instant. Because they are all fundamentally different things that are not interchangeable.If you are working with timezones for times in the future you should\n\n\n\nSince all three are based on epoch times, and working with epoch times is lossy.I would recommend using a DateTime library that handles this properly (Such as jsJoda), and persist the actual YMDHMS values into the database."]},
{"question": "Adding Disallowed Deprecations to Rails 6.1", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "5 Common Mistakes Developers Do that Affect Page Load Time", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Vimeo Engineering: It\u2019s not legacy code \u2014 it\u2019s PHP", "details": "", "answers": ["I'm just here to watch this comment thread devolve into \"LOL PHP\"Joking aside I appreciate their decision. I personally haven't touched PHP in like ~4-5 years and don't necessarily miss it, but I think it is cool that they didn't just jump on the hype train of something else and rewrite their entire platform in it instead of sticking with what is working for them and what they knew could have been better and  become better. I hear really good things about PHP in its current version."]},
{"question": "Best Programming Languages to Learn in 2021", "details": "", "answers": ["Badly researched imo"]},
{"question": "Codechef ATM Problem : How to solve your first Codechef problem", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "HTML code for the table", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Sonarqube: What it is and why to use it?", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "History of .net from a PL perspective", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Token authentication requirements for Git operations - The GitHub Blog", "details": "", "answers": ["If you use GitHub Enterprise Server,  to our on-premises offering.Emphasis added. This sounds like a passive-aggressive jab at development not managing to communicate about changes. \"We may have changes but nobody told me.\""]},
{"question": "Evalon4J v1.0.0 has been released, it's an awesome tool for generating java api documentation", "details": "", "answers": ["If you are the author (or a user), would you mind adding some details about what this actually generates?Is the idea that you add this to your build process and it generates .md files that other devs can browse through my GitHub repo?"]},
{"question": "Holiday Entertainment: The Best Books, T.V. Shows, and Movies For Programmers", "details": "", "answers": [""]},
{"question": "compute (literal) clouds from randomness \u2014 open source", "details": "", "answers": ["The end result looks awesome. Cool method too"]},
{"question": "Three things I wish I knew before becoming a software developer -- Especially as a woman in tech! \ud83d\udc69\u200d\ud83d\udcbb", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Way of doing click event in the HTML button.", "details": "", "answers": ["Probably better suited to "]},
{"question": "Centering in CSS", "details": "", "answers": ["If you have to support IE, you can't use grid. I wish the author included caniuse metrics as a factor."]},
{"question": "Chrome Extensions Every Web Developer Needs", "details": "", "answers": ["Article doesn't have date so I can't tell if this is from today or 10 years ago, sure looks to be tips from 10 years ago with a focus on non-web specific development related tools.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n"]},
{"question": "Sidebar navigation in visual studio Blend", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to Migrate Data In MongoDB?", "details": "", "answers": ["I wish that went more into the limitations and performance.We are currently sitting on ~2.9 billion documents in our main collection (the others are smaller, never going much about a two-digit million count, also the actual documents are smaller), and I doubt we'd want to dump that. :P\nSure, we got systems in place for our replication, backup and disaster recovery, but given that Mongo only excels when you need to hold a lot of data somewhere and need to write into it very quickly, it'd be nice to know where the cutoff point was, for a newcomer."]},
{"question": "C++20 Published (ISO/IEC 14882:2020)", "details": "", "answers": ["TL;DR?What does it bring?"]},
{"question": "Shitlist Driven Development (Dec 2016)", "details": "", "answers": ["I'm a big proponent of Depression Driven Design."]},
{"question": "VkResample - real-time Vulkan FFT upscaling", "details": "", "answers": ["The quality of the FFT is pretty damn good. Very interesting. Fourier transforms have always been the coolest thing to me. The fact that any continuous function can be approximated by adding sine waves is just too beautiful."]},
{"question": "Amazon Enters the Geospatial Landscape with Amazon Location", "details": "", "answers": ["Eww, this sounds like big-brother evil-corp. Now every shop-owner and leech can piggyback on Amazons predatory surveillance of ordinary people. We are approaching something like personalized ads in the public space. Pretty yucky 'service' imho.."]},
{"question": "51% of 4 million Docker images have critical vulnerabilities", "details": "", "answers": ["Interesting premise, but the article itself is reasonably useless."]},
{"question": "Learn about docker networking and tutorial about bridge networking in docker.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Yesterday's Google outage was due to automated quota management reducing capacity on their IdM", "details": "", "answers": ["Many of our internal users and tools experienced similar errors, which added delaysThis is the part I was thinking about! With Gmail inaccessible, how'd they email each other about the fix? lol."]},
{"question": "Myths about /dev/urandom", "details": "", "answers": ["Can someone explain to me what this entropy feedback thing is in /dev/random? How can \"entropy\" run low?My intuition is the following: Once I manage to somehow generate something akin to a good 128-bit AES key, I can use it to generate an infinite sequence of \"random\" numbers with some block cipher scheme. I never need to block anymore (until reboot or whatever). I'd really like to see someone who can then predict as this point what the next generated random number is. So where does this entropy-is-running-low story now come into play once I have established a good random seed (here the 128-bit aes key)?"]},
{"question": "XS-Leaks Wiki", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Building a game with TypeScript. Input system 1/3", "details": "", "answers": ["What an over engineered engine for such a simple game. I know, I know, it's about writing a generic engine and the game is just a simple example. But I actually think writing generic engines is dumb in most cases. Unless you want to create a generic engine, the engine should be spec'ed to game you want to make.And, starting out with data structures before even implementing basic functionalities is plain dumb. A better approach is to work on X feature until you are an \"expert\" on that module and know *exactly* what is needed in terms of data structures and code. Data types will form naturally and is a way more efficient and arguably easier method to creating complex systems."]},
{"question": "I curated a list of links to post your side projects!", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Malicious Domain in SolarWinds Hack Turned into \u2018Killswitch\u2019", "details": "", "answers": ["I wonder if anybody is going to be held responsible for this incident. It looks like several major government agencies were hacked and who knows what our enemies (or friends I guess) have on us now."]},
{"question": "Interactive Mandelbrot set visualizer in Go", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Design Patterns Overview", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Security Flaw Heat Map", "details": "", "answers": ["I'm looking at C++ and the top one is error handling. Not \"buffer\" and not \"memory safety\". I found that strange. So then I guessed maybe the error handling arises from signed/unsigned pollution, but \"numeric errors\" are a separate entry. Maybe I write code weird or I don't understand the C++ community like I thought I did?"]},
{"question": "Json Parser Online - Json Beautifier, Formatter & Validator", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Improving Cross-Browser Testing, Part 1: Web Application Testing Today", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Becoming a Time Lord in Raku", "details": "", "answers": ["Nice. I'm a complete Raku noob but write lots of perl. Mind teaching me how to RTFM?Foo.^find_method('bar').wrap(\n    method (|c) {\n        say \"Called 'bar' with arguments \", c;\n        my $result = callsame;\n        say \"  --> \", $result;\n        $result;\n    }\n);\nI understand we're wrapping Foo's bar method.But how do I find out what the ^ and the | are doing?"]},
{"question": ".NET On QA [Has the time come for a new StackOverflow?]", "details": "", "answers": ["Personally, the day Stack Overflow dies will be a good day.The gamification idea that Atwood had helped it grow, but it certainly didn't help it build a decent community.  Can you imagine if all the students in your school were hall monitors, monitoring each other all day, every day?Giving software developers a rulebook that they can enforce on others is never going to be a good idea.  We as a group are the very epitome of skilled rules lawyers.My favorite anecdote about SO is when I asked a question about a UPC.  It got moved to a different SO site and then THAT SO site closed it as not relevant.  Which is true, it wasn't relevant, I had put it on the SO site that  WAS relevant so I wasn't even mad about it getting closed I just laughed my ass off.SO as a resource isn't terrible, but the community really really sucks and you eventually get to a point in your career where you're working on stuff no one will be able to really help with on SO because it's way more subtle and nuanced than trying to figure out how to get react to give handjobs."]},
{"question": "Visualizing Data using Leaflet and Netlify", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "decentralizing the software supply chain via reproducible builds", "details": "", "answers": ["BLUF:It's a Go program that does something with Nix.Trustix compares build outputs for given build inputs across independent providers and machinesI don't understand why the different providers can't just do that themselves."]},
{"question": "My friend and I made an application for controlling a computer from a browser. Today we have 8000 users!", "details": "", "answers": ["Notable lack of information about security.  Or anything that appears to have something to do with programming."]},
{"question": "Static calls in Linux 5.10", "details": "", "answers": ["It's pretty common to have function pointers that change infrequently or not at all once written. This is a great technique for transforming such cases from indirect to direct calls.I'd be excited to see if it could be extended to runtime devirtualization in C++ for limited cases or not."]},
{"question": "The definitive iTerm2 & Oh-my-ZSH Setup on macOS", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "(X-POST r/datascience) Airflow 2.0 has been released", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Refactoring, Unit Tests, and Symmathesy", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Coding Bootcamp Graduate works in JAPAN as a Software Engineer | Developer Stories", "details": "", "answers": ["Who wouldn't want to work in a country that has to have a special word for \"death from overwork\" because it's so prevalent..."]},
{"question": "Ajax and XHR using plain JS", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Creating Simple Local Python Packages with __init__.py", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "3 Tips To Overcome The XY Problem", "details": "", "answers": ["Another paywall'd Medium post. Folks, there are plenty of free blogging platforms that anyone can just look at without having to sign in."]},
{"question": "Create RDS Dashboards on Grafana with the AWS CloudWatch Datasource", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Best 10 affordable laptops for coding. - ucompare.in", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Extension to auto pause background audio,video if active tab has audio", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Expanding Fuchsia's open source model", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": ".NET Has a Third-Party Software Problem", "details": "", "answers": ["Nuget says differently. I think this article skews the problem that some companies that don't like risk, revolve around Microsoft because they are seen as a trusted source. These companies are not representative of the .NET ecosystem community."]},
{"question": "Learn Java by building 17 projects step by step", "details": "", "answers": ["First step, pay"]},
{"question": "To the brain, reading computer code is not the same as reading language", "details": "", "answers": ["There was already a discussion about this 2 days ago: "]},
{"question": "The future of Infrastructure as Code is VB.NET", "details": "", "answers": ["Considering Microsoft isn't really investing in the language further, I'm willing to bet it's not."]},
{"question": "To the brain, reading computer code is not the same as reading language", "details": "", "answers": ["A cardinal sin of academic reporting: .I haven\u2019t fully read the paper, but I skimmed it for participant details:\n\n\n\nI do wonder if such a small, localized sample can be representative of the general population, but also if different languages would yield different results."]},
{"question": "Affine Transformations \u2014 Pan, Zoom, Skew. From the context of the HTML Canvas.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Introducing Cloudflare Pages: the best way to build JAMstack websites", "details": "", "answers": ["Idk what this is"]},
{"question": "I've walked away from software development", "details": "", "answers": ["I don\u2019t care."]},
{"question": "bbacklight - When xbacklight doesn't want to collaborate", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "TiDB on KubeSphere: Release a Cloud-Native Distributed Database to the KubeSphere App Store", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Top 7 Best Ways to Learn Programming From The Scratch", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Best Angularjs Development Tools for Developers", "details": "", "answers": ["There seems to be a lot of confusion in this blog post. Angular is obsolete. Nowadays you should use Angular (formerly Angular 2).s/Angularjs/Angular/g"]},
{"question": "Chrome Extension Tutorial \u2014 Replace Images in Any Website with Pikachu", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Automatic Syntax Error Recovery for LR Parsers", "details": "", "answers": ["I personally dislike the use of videos to display compiler output. I have to sit and wait 5-10 seconds for the text to appear before I can continue reading. :/"]},
{"question": "How to do Data Visualization in Python for Data Science", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Problem: Run a different function if the first condition is not met. Thanks in advance ;D", "details": "", "answers": ["My first suggestion would be that you followed a basic tutorial taking you through the basics of programming.You got a suggestion to write a function and pass an integer as a parameter, and If you are unable to understand that, this tells me that you need some fundamentals before proceeding."]},
{"question": "Pure Go Unikernels - go metal with TamaGo", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Issue15 -Everything I Automated In 2020 To Save Me Hours Of Time", "details": "", "answers": ["What? I was looking forward to reading about someone's personal experience automating tasks, and instead got a list of newsletters and other articles."]},
{"question": "Made a tool that determines the Big-O complexity of your code!", "details": "", "answers": ["It's a neat idea but a lot of Big-O is really tough, for example the sieve of eratosthenes:for (int i = 2; i * i < n; i++)\n    if (!arr[i])\n        for (int j = i * 2; j < n; j += i)\n            arr[j] = true;\nWhere the outer loop is O(sqrt(N)) (and reported as O(n) in the app) but the algorithm as a whole is O(n log log n) because the runtime is  (and errors out in the app).I'm unsure if proving the Big-O complexity of just for-loops is undecidable (I'd wager the easiest way to tell would be to try and write the halting problem with only for-loops, which is known to be undecidable) but generally finding the Big-O of algorithms can be hell."]},
{"question": "Why Java Is Dying", "details": "", "answers": ["For some reason I have a feeling that I will see articles with the same title in 2040 and later."]},
{"question": "How to Manage Your Data the Way You Manage Your Code", "details": "", "answers": ["Nice approach"]},
{"question": "WebAuthn: A Guide To Authenticate Your Application", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "History of Pascal", "details": "", "answers": ["\"\u2026I saw it as  [pdf], updated to the requirements of the time\u2026\""]},
{"question": "GTK 4.0 released", "details": "", "answers": ["I just want to clear this up since multiple people have been complaining about it.GTK has support for native dialogs through GtkNativeDialog since 3.20. This includes GtkFileChooserNative. So if you are on Windows or Mac you will get the correct dialog and if you are on KDE you will get the correct dialog. It is up to maintainers to opt into these classes though.Electron has an open PR for fixing this that can hopefully be merged soon."]},
{"question": "Great reward for someone who can bypass Geocomply or leads us to someone who will succeed on that", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "ANOTHER RANDOM PROJECT FLOW FIELD (Android Processing APDE)", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "new GCC plug-in for AFL++ and advanced fuzz testing on Ada", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "All my programming threads and job hunting resources in one list", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to set up a Smashing dashboard on your Raspberry Pi", "details": "", "answers": ["I went down this path, and while it was ok I didn't think it handled weird resolutions well, and I wanted something kind of specific with Google Calendar that wasn't trivial to pull off.  I ended up going with  which has a nice web portal to manage it, and even has a raspbian image with the software preloaded."]},
{"question": "Exploring wikipedia with Python", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "'Coins' extension on VSCode", "details": "", "answers": ["No"]},
{"question": "HEADS UP: FreeBSD src repo transitioning from Subversion to Git this weekend (2020-12-17)", "details": "", "answers": ["Glad to see it. Dragonfly has been using git this entire time, so seeing the fork parent move more fully to git is nice."]},
{"question": "Commits are shapshots, not diffs - The GitHub Blog", "details": "", "answers": ["I can understand why people might think they're diffs, since that's how git show presents them."]},
{"question": "CI/CD quick tip: Lock pull requests in an incident", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Lightmeter: Release candidate: 1.1.0-RC1", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Google Search URL Filter", "details": "", "answers": ["I didn't get that yet \ud83e\udd14\ud83d\udc94"]},
{"question": "Best 5 Prestigious Programming Contests.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to add dark mode to your website in less than 5 minutes - I\u2019m sharing the code I use for all my projects. Just copy and paste it into your projects. I even have a styled toggle button To place anywhere and it\u2019ll work. Hope it\u2019s useful to anyone! No frameworks. Just vanilla code.", "details": "", "answers": ["Use @media (prefers-color-scheme: dark)"]},
{"question": "Poser - Create mock endpoints populated with fake data easily", "details": "", "answers": ["I want to see what this is all about, but I don't want to log in via github just to read some documentation or see what it is.Consider exposing docs / basic info without requiring a login."]},
{"question": "Interview with React Query's creator: Tanner Linsley", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Making a Linked List in C/C++ in XCode", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "A minimal and easy-to-use C testing framework, in plain C with no dependencies", "details": "", "answers": ["What is with C and abbreviated namespaces/names?"]},
{"question": "Kubernetes 1.21 Release Team Shadow Application", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "I made a simple Secret Santa telegram bot for me and my friends and thought i'd share it with you guys in case anyone needs it!", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to Defend Against AWS Surprise Bills", "details": "", "answers": ["By using Digital Ocean. That is what I did."]},
{"question": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0631\u0646\u0627\u0645\u062c \u062c\u0648\u0645\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u0639\u062f\u064a\u0644 \u062e\u0635\u0627\u0626\u0635 \u0645\u062d\u0631\u0631 \u062c\u064a \u0633\u064a \u0627\u064a | Joomla JCE Editor Proprieties", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Should we turn our readmes into interactive notebooks?", "details": "", "answers": ["I'm just happy people include readmes in their repos."]},
{"question": "How I Easily Code For 8 Hours Without Feeling Tired (My Productivity System)", "details": "", "answers": ["Trucker speed?But in all seriousness this system works I guess if you're self employed. A good part of my day is partially set by the company filled with meetings, stand-ups and whatnot. A manager could even demand you switch over to something else because it got higher priority."]},
{"question": "Garmin Watch Faces: Custom Fonts", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Help me with this Question [JAVA]", "details": "", "answers": ["You're fired"]},
{"question": "100 Days of Code", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0631\u0646\u0627\u0645\u062c \u062c\u0648\u0645\u0644\u0627 \u0627\u0636\u0627\u0641\u0629 \u0635\u0648\u0631\u0629 \u0644\u0645\u0642\u062f\u0645\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u0627\u0644\u0629 \u0648\u0627\u0644\u0643\u0627\u0645\u0644\u0629 | Joomla Adding Pic...", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Hallucinations re: the rendering of Cyberpunk 2077", "details": "", "answers": ["Two curses befall rendering engineers. First, we lose the ability to look at reality without being constantly reminded of how fascinatingly hard it is to solve light transport and model materials.Second, when you start playing any game, you cannot refrain from trying to reverse its rendering technology This hurts because it's so true."]},
{"question": "I built a tool for collaborative task prioritization, still experimental but would love feedback", "details": "", "answers": ["Doesn't work on mobile"]},
{"question": "WebGL is awesome: a scene I made during my day off", "details": "", "answers": ["Another \"step further\" might be to synchronize it to the beat of the music."]},
{"question": "Chris Krebs C# Log Explained", "details": "", "answers": ["haha, that was funny"]},
{"question": "Found this goldmine of a youtube channel. I dont know him, he doesnt know me but I see he puts a lot of effort into his videos and I think he deserves some attention.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Starting today, GitHub Code Search will only index repositories that have had recent activity within the last year.", "details": "", "answers": ["Speaking as a person who searches through old Github repos, looking for people who have reverse-engineered various Bluetooth device protocols, I'm a little sad. Often a person will have spent a fair bit of time and effort trying to figure out how to control some obscure device (and in the Bluetooth space, most devices are obscure). Then they are nice enough to write a little Python app (or similar).Right now it's often easy to find these bits of code: you just look up the Bluetooth services and characteristics by GUID. If the original developer did their job and used new, random GUIDs, you'll often find enough hints to figure out how to drive the device.But I can't imagine there are that many people doing this. Result: all that hard-won knowledge will be lost.(Given that, I can also imagine this will cut down on the number of Github searches that return results from someone's comp-101 class projects)"]},
{"question": "An intuition for Python metaclasses", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Why we use JOOQ instead of Hibernate", "details": "", "answers": ["The one place where ORMs shine is doing simple CRUD operations. In this case, just assigning some fields to an object and calling .save() on it is far simpler than manually generating INSERT statements.It's not \"far simpler\", it's \"marginally simpler\".  The ORM is only capable of handling the most trivial of cases, those which require zero reasoning on the part of the developer to implement manually, anyway.Shit, there might already be a plugin for your favorite IDE that can auto-gen these.  I care so little about the \"problem\" of having to write an SQL query that I have never even bothered to look.All the bloat and opacity that comes with something like Hibernate is a terrible trade-off."]},
{"question": "Coding Log app(100% free for ever), best solution to track, analyze and share how much you code! - Made in flutter", "details": "", "answers": ["What, besides a timer, is it?Because it seems like you start a timer tagged with a language and then end it. And then you can see the length of the various timers sliced in various ways."]},
{"question": "Learning to program a computer is similar to learning a new language. However, MIT neuroscientists found that reading computer code does not activate language processing brain regions. Instead, it activates a network for complex cognitive tasks such as solving math problems or crossword puzzles.", "details": "", "answers": ["I've been programming in several different languages for ages and I still struggle with foreign languages.  My problem is I want them to be logical and they aren't."]},
{"question": "When do you dive deep? Your confusion is the litmus test", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Day 18: Typed Raku, Part 1: Taming State - Ben Davies", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "A simple example of good taste in code", "details": "", "answers": ["Oh fuck this article. I don't understand how someone forks it to clean it and and still have the same major fuck upDo people not understand pointer pointers are used in different situation than pointers? Do you all never catch for(int i=0; i<=end; i++) errors?"]},
{"question": "AnimXYZ \u2014 A Composable CSS Animation Toolkit For React, Vue, Plain HTML & CSS", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "iOS 14.3 Brings WebRTC to WKWebView, Closing Gap on iOS Accessibility", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "SQLite 2020 Status Report (presentation starts around 11:00)", "details": "", "answers": ["Slides: "]},
{"question": "5 frequently used tag", "details": "", "answers": [""]},
{"question": "11 Best Bug Bounty Platform for Beginners in 2020 - TechyEverything", "details": "", "answers": ["List is good, can you suggest me one I can start with"]},
{"question": "Writing a custom iterator in modern C++", "details": "", "answers": ["concepts since C++20. For example, instead of the std::forward_iterator_tag tag you would mark your iterator with the std::forward_iterator concept......I will upgrade the article as soon as the concept implementation will become more widespread.!remindme 5 years"]},
{"question": "VMware Flaw a Vector in SolarWinds Breach?", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Extremist Programming", "details": "", "answers": ["Note that this is from 2012."]},
{"question": "I wrote a series of articles comparing OOP and FP from a very practical standpoint. Modern general-purpose languages support both of the paradigms. Being conscious of that and choosing the right style for your use case is vital for ending up with an elegant and maintainable system.", "details": "", "answers": ["This is not OOP vs FP. This is dynamic dispatch vs. static functions."]},
{"question": "Buy Don't Build: Avoiding Ops For Fun and Profit", "details": "", "answers": ["I always enjoy reading articles like this and in general agree with them.  I would just say don't go buying SAP!!!!"]},
{"question": "Learn about ghapi, a new third-party Python client for the GitHub API - The GitHub Blog", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Playmaker: The Reality of 10x Engineer", "details": "", "answers": ["I like this take on the 10x meme"]},
{"question": "John Carmack \u2014 Career advice", "details": "", "answers": ["This isn't even advice, it's just some random thought he had. Has he ever even had to apply for a job?"]},
{"question": "I mean, this is one way to do it :))", "details": "", "answers": ["Can't believe they passed all those parameters by value instead of by reference. Waste, waste, waste.\n That's my only complaint."]},
{"question": "Learn Coding for FREE \ud83d\udcaf Easiest Way to Learn Latest Programming Languages with Certificate \ud83d\udc4f", "details": "", "answers": ["You can learn almost all Coding Languages which are in demand currently.. You can practice what you learn from within the app .. Comment me if you have any issues using this app .."]},
{"question": "Learn in public", "details": "", "answers": ["Get taught by experts, learn with experts, become the expert. Do not be downtrodden by uninitiated opinions"]},
{"question": "Just a tiny script to help you build old coreutils versions on modern systems", "details": "", "answers": ["I like the thumbnail."]},
{"question": "Building A Fantasy Game Console Emulator: System Overview and Graphics Pipeline", "details": "", "answers": ["Looks dope!"]},
{"question": "Keyboard navigation in Android Studio / IntelliJ", "details": "", "answers": ["Personally I feel like \"{\" and \"}\" are super useful navigation tools, so I map those to \"J\" and \"K\" (that way, all of my vertical navigation is some combination of capital and lowercase js and ks)"]},
{"question": "Make Your Own E-mail Spoofer Script And Send E-mails As Anyone You Want To Be", "details": "", "answers": ["Ah, so SMTP is still SMTP.  Good, everything is working as intended.If the company or person you're pretending to be or even just the person you're targeting has  email protections set up, this will fail so hard your target won't even know you tried to email them.SPF, DKIM, DMARC, DNSBL/RBL and other such acronyms exist because this has been common knowledge among people administering email services since the late 90s. Your dreamhost server won't be able to send email to any Gmail or Outlook address, ever. You need a positive reliability rating for your email to be delivered, which means you need to send people a whole bunch of actual, real emails, before your email even comes in without being marked as spam. If you change hosts/IP addresses, you need to build that reputation up from the ground again.Trust me, I'm running my own mail server for my legitimate personal email and I can't get people to receive my mail without hitting some kind of blacklist. Your email script will just pollute the internet further without accomplishing anything.By the way, what's the point of starting a session here? Why do you do string concatenation like this instead of just \"From:  $fromname <$fromemail>\"?Also, your script is vulnerable for XSS because you echo back a variable from the query parameters without filtering out HTML characters first. If you store this script on any (sub)domain you use for real stuff, like a WordPress blog, you're two clicks away from getting tricked into leaking your cookies if you click a link to your own website.Now, for people who want to do phishing tests themselves (very useful in a corporate setting), use a tool such as GoPhish, CatPhish, ReelPhish or similar in combination with Evilginx or Modlishka and be sure to set up the necessary SPF/DKIM/DMARC configuration. No need to write your own email scripts if you want to simulate malicious behaviour!"]},
{"question": "Double Blind Passwords (aka Horcruxing)", "details": "", "answers": ["Interesting but wouldn't your password manager ask if you want to update your password every time you login with that technique?"]},
{"question": "Norman Abramson, information theorist and creator of the Ethernet precursor ALOHAnet (shared access wireless packet network), dead at 88", "details": "", "answers": ["This is devastating. My research is based on his work. I was lucky enough to meet him a couple of years back at MOBICOM and he was the nicest guy. This is a terrible loss for the CS community."]},
{"question": "Highest Paying Programming Languages", "details": "", "answers": ["BS article. Stopped reading after they claimed rails a programming language"]},
{"question": "Battery prices have fallen 88 percent over the last decade", "details": "", "answers": ["So laptops and smartphones should be cheaper, right? \ud83d\ude00Why is this posted to ?"]},
{"question": "Redis Cluster - Benefits of Sharding and How It Works", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Precise Typing Implies Functional Programming", "details": "", "answers": ["ADTs are one way to precisely model type semantics. Without proof1, I will assert that they are actually the only way..\nIf I\u2019m wrong on this, please point it out in the comments.I believe OOP type hierarchies can also precisely encode JSON semantics (or anything union types also can) with the simple addition of a limiting clause as to what sub-types are allowed (as Kotlin does and Java will soon add)... does that make OOP type hierarchies ADTs? I guess it kind of does, but I find it interesting that the two things are not that distant in the first place.precise types \u21d2 functional programming.\nfunctional programming \u21cf precise types.Honestly, I think FP and precise types are completely orthogonal. Even purity (which does affect the notion of precise types) does not seem unique to FP. Rust was given as an example of a language that has fairly precise types and is definitely not functional (but has elements usually characteristic of FP, like pure functions with \"const fn\" and ADTs with \"enum\"). D is another.... even Zig (I mean, it's as far from FP as it can be, being a \"better C\") has \"pure functions\".Meanwhile, Clojure and Erlang are firmly in the FP camp but have no compile-time type checks at all (I know, the first implication does not imply the second, false, implication - but why is it useful to say you end up with FP when you precisely specify your types, when you can also end up with FP when you don't??).EDIT: clarify my remarks about OOP hierarchies..."]},
{"question": "Best Websites to Find Free Resources for Frontend Web Developers and Designers", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Top programming languages", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Getting started with C programming a lightning-fast start for absolute beginners", "details": "", "answers": ["he absolute beginner technical guide may be the most difficult kind of writing there is. You have to know what's already in the head of the absolute beginner. If it's garbage, you need to set that straight before anything else can happen."]},
{"question": "I have created a 1-year-weekly-breakdown deck for full-stack web development (opinionated). Please check this out and give feedback to improve", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Is it possible if u help me review my resume as i want to get a tech internship after i complete my army? Would really appreciate it if u can give me feeback", "details": "", "answers": ["I have hired dozens of tech interns over the last 6 years for a programming internship at a medium sized US Federal agency. Here are my thoughts:Correct the spelling and grammatical issues.I'm not sure about the Summary section. I like seeing the passion, but I'm not sure it's appropriately written for a professional job. I generally see a Goals section that says \"To get a job in programming that best utilizes my knowledge, skills, and abilities.\" Maybe a hybrid approach that covers both the summary and Goals, but in a very succinct way.I would expand the Job Shadowing section (which I would also rename, shadowing implies you just watched, but it's apparent you did actual work.) You can add a bit about \"learning how a professional environment operates\" or more technical aspects of the job.On the Dengue Fever and Youtube sections, I would include the programming language you used (Python, presumably)Most of your experience appears to be with Python and Pandas (which I love, by the way). Seeing a larger breadth of experience would be helpful. Java is generally taught in most US schools, so I'm used to seeing Java first and other languages second. Having another language besides Python would show that you can adapt to another new language easier (for example, Dart, C++, etc.)I never find the Courses section to be useful, since all programming students take the same courses.As a general observation, what I look for in a potential intern is individuality, the ability to adapt and learn new things, and some basic knowledge of the initial conditions of the job (programming language, type of analysis, sector of work, etc.) For my job, if I saw the words \"Java, programming, analysis, and data\" on a resume, I would probably schedule an interview. In the interview I want to see confidence, know-how, and a personality (enthusiasm, humor, etc.)Think about what is going to set you apart from the other applicants (all of whom took the same courses). Emphasize those features. Get the point across that you do programming because you love it, you do it for fun, and not just for a job.Good luck!"]},
{"question": "Centering in CSS", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "CSS Thumbnail Effect", "details": "", "answers": ["Looks broken in chrome on iOS. The rounded corners are lost during animation."]},
{"question": "Abstractions Are In The Eye Of The Beholder", "details": "", "answers": ["Both examples are too low level to make any sense without more context. Seems like \u201cprimitive obsession\u201d in either case."]},
{"question": "What is a floating point number ?", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Any way to display live weather on Google slides / PowerPoint?", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "A demonstration of implementing resumable workflows in celery [Python]", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Getting started with Infrastructure as Code using AWS Cloudformation", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "A modern port of Turbo Vision 2.0, the classical framework for text-based user interfaces. Now cross-platform and with Unicode support.", "details": "", "answers": ["Nice work!Brings back so many memories of simpler times ..."]},
{"question": "Automatically Overlaying Baseball Pitch Motion and Trajectory with ML", "details": "", "answers": ["This project takes your baseball pitching clips and  generates the overlay. A fine-tuned Yolov4 model is used to get the location of the ball. Then, I implemented SORT tracking algorithm to keep track of each individual ball and filter out the misdetection noise. Lastly, I have applied some image registration techniques to deal with slight camera shift on each clip.I'm still trying to improve it! Feel free to follow this project, also check out the Todo list.BTW, I just want to point out that did anyone notice that the pitcher throw the ball with the  posture but it turned out to fly on a completely different path. It's just amazing!"]},
{"question": "Which languages should I learn? (my opinion)", "details": "", "answers": ["Russian"]},
{"question": "My experience of working in enterprise. It's my first attempt to write something so be easy on me. Also share your thoughts", "details": "", "answers": ["Try writing about something you have experience with."]},
{"question": "Getting started in Python 3 programming - Some usefull resources", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Active-Active PostgreSQL Federation on Kubernetes", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Production Debugging: Everything You Need to Know", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Bharat Mediratta - The Story of Google Web Server (and more)", "details": "", "answers": ["Loved this quote in the end: \"It was a mixed bag of amazing and horrific, and probably still is\"."]},
{"question": "Pragmalang 0.2.0 Released - The Language For Building GraphQL APIs In No Time", "details": "", "answers": ["Hey people! I just want to say that your feedback is greatly appreciated. Please don't shy away from writing whatever comes to your mind. I'd love to read your criticisms and thoughts."]},
{"question": "Dockerrizing Tensorflow for Accessibility", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Implementing an Effective Architecture for ASP.NET Core Web API", "details": "", "answers": ["Why do your ViewModels/Entities not use constructors to convert between the two?"]},
{"question": "\ud83d\ude80 Fast and low HTTP router and URL matcher for building Deno servers \ud83e\udd95.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Infographics about career opportunity in programming", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Feedback on the Log4J2 hack in Spring Boot", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Patch commutation and scalability", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Ryzen 5800X vs Apple M1: Programming-focused benchmarks", "details": "", "answers": ["It's still wild to me that M1 can compare with top x86 processors on this level"]},
{"question": "A new release for GNU Octave [LWN.net]", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Best 5 books for cracking the coding interview.", "details": "", "answers": ["Leetcode is bullshit.The \u201c10x developer\u201d this is a literal bullshit fantasy dreamed up by nerd who get their dick hard thinking about algorithms. Software is a creative endeavor. Jerking yourself off in an interview does nothing to prove your value."]},
{"question": "PJON - Networking freedom for hackers and experimenters", "details": "", "answers": ["More info here: "]},
{"question": "Odd Even Linked List", "details": "", "answers": ["Ok, I'll bite. It's not a particularly good or bad tutorial but damn is it a disappointing one. So much wasted potential.First issue: It's about singly linked lists, which aren't used in the real world except as an immutable data structure. This tutorial uses a mutable version, which combines the performance of a linked list with the persistence of an array to solve the real world problems of nothing. If it was immutable, you could've compared the implementations of plain C, Haskell (laziness), OCaml (textbook recursion, possible stack overflow), SML (tail calls and additional calls to reverse) and ATS (hole data structures/recursion). That would probably be enough for a blog post already.Second issue: This tutorial solves ONE specific problem, which, again, has no real world use outside of coding interviews. Maybe. But it's so simple to make the solution more general: solve the problem by writing a filter or partition function instead. Now you can explain higher order functions, lambdas, generics and composition as well as the solution.Third: The headline reads like this post was about a novel data structure with interesting properties, which it isn't."]},
{"question": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0631\u0646\u0627\u0645\u062c \u062c\u0648\u0645\u0644\u0627 [ \u062a\u063a\u064a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0639\u062f\u0627\u062f\u0627\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u0627\u0644\u0627\u062a \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062a\u0639\u0627\u0631\u064a\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0627\u0645\u0629 ] | Globa...", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Miui 12.5 update", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0631\u0646\u0627\u0645\u062c \u062c\u0648\u0645\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u063a\u064a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0639\u062f\u0627\u062f\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u0627\u0644\u0629 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629 | Joomla Change Articl...", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Technical Deep Dive: Reducing Memory Consumption in Visual Assist build 2393", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "ClickHouse and S3 Compatible Object Storage", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0631\u0646\u0627\u0645\u062c \u062c\u0648\u0645\u0644\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0631\u0642 \u0628\u064a\u0646 Joomla Page Heading VS Titles Vs Browse Page...", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to Learn Python For Data Science", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0631\u0646\u0627\u0645\u062c \u062c\u0648\u0645\u0644\u0627 \u062a\u063a\u064a\u064a\u0631 \u0627\u0639\u062f\u0627\u062f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u0627\u0644\u0629 \u0645\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u0627\u0644\u0629 \u0646\u0641\u0633\u0647\u0627 | Change Article ...", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Help wanted - Building a high-performance GraphQL server with Go to expose Stack Overflow data", "details": "", "answers": ["I'm actively working on this so add an issue / send a message if you want to build this out!"]},
{"question": "Hi, has anybody of you used Rocket web framework for Rust? If yes, how it is different from the others? Currently I am using Node, Django and RoR. What is the plus of using Rocket? I know i can read the docs, but I want some information from developers who are using it in real world scenarios.", "details": "", "answers": [" or  would be better places for this question. This subreddit is mostly for industry news and tech demos/tutorials rather than questions."]},
{"question": "Visualise, document and explore your software architecture - Simon Brown", "details": "", "answers": ["Watched the whole thing, thanks for sharing. Very elegant and practical approach to starting to address the model / code gap. I\u2019m curious to see how the tools supporting this philosophy  have evolved since 2017."]},
{"question": "Hi everyone, i'm a gamedev. I just released the hardest game, if you enjoy the content you can subscribe cause that helps me a lot :)", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Make the nice list with JSDoc", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Database Multi-Tenancy For\u00c2 SaaS", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Understanding Facebook\u2019s ReBeL \u2014 A Noteworthy Step in Artificial General Intelligence", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Distributed SQLite with Blockchain", "details": "", "answers": ["Oh god."]},
{"question": "Create space in HTML", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "2020\u2019s Top 15 Machine Learning & AI Research Papers", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Tips to become more productive as a vim newbie", "details": "", "answers": ["Tip 1 that helped me, play "]},
{"question": "\ud83d\ude80 Fast and low HTTP router and URL matcher for building Deno servers \ud83e\udd95.", "details": "", "answers": ["Not a huge fan of that API... at all; why not just a simple app.addRoute({}) all other details can be inferred and don't need to be exposed to users.r.WithMethods(RequestMethod.GET)\n    .Path(\"/hello\")\n    .HandleFunc(async function (Request: HttpRequest, ResponseWriter: HttpResponse) {\n      ResponseWriter.WithBody(\"Hello Xanny\").Return();\n    })\n    .Path(\"/demo\")\n    .HandleFunc(async function (Request: HttpRequest, ResponseWriter: HttpResponse) {\n      ResponseWriter.WithBody(\"Hello Xanny Demo\").Return();\n    });\ncould then becomeapp.route({\n    Method: RequestMethod.GET,\n    Path: '/hello',\n    HandleFunc: async (Request, ResponseWriter, HttpResponse) => {\n        ResponseWriter.WithBody('Hello Xanny').Return();\n    }\n}).route({\n    Method: RequestMethod.GET,\n    Path: '/demo',\n    HandleFunc: async (Request, ResponseWriter, HttpResponse) => {\n        ResponseWriter.WithBody('Hello Xanny Demo').Return();\n    }\n})\nand I can then just cut out  const r = app.NewRoute({ maxRoutes:2 });Since you can then just do whatever implementation work as needed.I also am not a huge fan of the code style... seems very foreign to me for Typescript; at the very least follow the Deno style-guide Anyhow, my 2 cents."]},
{"question": "Technical Air Pollution: The Reality of Technical Debt", "details": "", "answers": ["The article spends no time at all explaining why \"technical debt\" is a bad metaphor.  At the top, you basically say \"I don't think this is good\" and offer no explanation why.  What deficiency does Cunningham's metaphor contain that you feel is lacking?  And although I know nobody has ever validated \"technical debt\" to be a good concept, what evidence would you supply that this model is better?  Neither of these questions are answered by this post in a way that's clear to me.Also, I think you ignore some realities about financial debt that are applicable to software: namely, .  Some debt is more correctly known as \"leverage\" and I wish more developers understood that some debt is worth the interest."]},
{"question": "Observability Getting Started \u2013 50 Free Access and Open-Source Solutions", "details": "", "answers": ["Solarwinds... Hmm, feel like I've heard that name somewhere else recently."]},
{"question": "Why .NET Standard Is Still Relevant", "details": "", "answers": ["Had a rude awakening when I tried to use a .NET Standard 2.1 library I had been using with .NET Core in a legacy .NET Framework application..."]},
{"question": "Here's Why You Should Be Using Overrides in Chrome Devtools", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Static analysis with semgrep: practical examples using Docker", "details": "", "answers": ["Stupid question. What's the significance of using Docker with semgrep?Like why would you set it up in Docker?Thanks"]},
{"question": "Made our subscription management system open source after our startup failed", "details": "", "answers": ["Hubble offered an easy-to-integrate subscription management service to startups and businesses, with a variety of customer acquisition and retention tools (or at least they were in our product road map). We participated in Y-Combinator Build Sprint in our second month. Ultimately we ceased operations as we did not find a USP.We made our source code opensource today under Apache License. I hope someone finds it useful, either as a learning material or for their own business. You can contact me at [](mailto:) if you have any queries or would like to contribute or take over the project.PS: If you are aware of problems that Hubble aligns with, please let me know. I would still love to work on it.  UPDATE: We changed the name from Hubble to Paywall. Here's the new link: "]},
{"question": "Experimenting with git storage", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "I'm organizing a webinar on how to manage application configurations in scaling teams.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "9 Interactive Python Libraries for Visualizing Data You Should Know", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Behind The 2020s\u2019 Biggest Breakthrough in Artificial Intelligence", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "NADAM Optimizer from Scratch in Python", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Tech stack #10YearChallenge", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "MS follows Apple with proprietary Chips", "details": "", "answers": ["This is not .However Microsoft is probably more interested in the Azure market then for Surface devices (of course it could do both). Moving to more efficient CPUs would be a good way of cutting down on their electricity bills."]},
{"question": "Torus Trooper - Rebooting a 15 year-old game written in D", "details": "", "answers": ["I remembered a game I played while at university 15 years ago. For a long time, I couldn\u2019t remember the name at all, only that it was from a Japanese developer. After some search wrangling, I finally managed to find the name of the game: Torus Trooper!Same here.I remembered its name and found its website but was disappointed that it only had windows binaries. Didn't bother to try to compile it from source.The link to the final product is at the end of part4 of the seriesSource code at Really well done job. It works just like before. Reminds me of the old days!"]},
{"question": "28hr work week - Jobs with a better work / life balance", "details": "", "answers": ["Launching soon, get notifiedIt's a sales funnel"]},
{"question": "Fast Static Symbol Table (FSST): fast text compression that allows random access, so individual strings can be decompressed without touching the surrounding data", "details": "", "answers": ["I'm don't understand how random access works.  If I ask for the 1000th character, how do you know which part of the compressed string that corresponds to?"]},
{"question": "Programming with Functions #2 - Functions as Data", "details": "", "answers": ["Every type fundamentally being represented by a number if you go down far enough doesn\u2019t actually mean you can just treat all data like numbers as the video implies. I get that it is fundamental to your argument that everything should be treated as a math equation, but this claim is just simply not true. Lol. There is literally nothing stopping an imperative programming language from implementing list comprehensions, and in fact, many do. Heck, there are even C libraries out there that provide strongly typed comprehensions with predicates.I mean, okay, in some cases you\u2019ll need to fall back to function pointers rather than closures since C doesn\u2019t have closures, but seriously...As an aside to the questionable at best information, you need a better microphone setup. So much popping."]},
{"question": "50 free tools and resources you're gonna love (Part 2)", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Simple first issue for intermediate programmers! (Basic Dart/API knowledge)", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Codespaces - Cloud-powered coding coming soon", "details": "", "answers": ["I love the idea of these, the latency is often annoying, but we might be there finally especially if you have fiber."]},
{"question": "Experimenting with Rust (WASM), WebGL and ReacJS \u2014 Textyle: Online Tilemap Editor", "details": "", "answers": ["Hello !I'm very exited to present you this tilemap editor I have been working during the past months.\n\n\nMy main goal is to provide the simplest way to build a tilemap. I was not happy with the existing solutions and didn't want to build an embedded editor to my engine, as it would be useful only for me.I used React JS for the UI, WebGL for the rendering and Rust compiled to WASM for the tilemap logic and algorithms. I think I was able to stablish a good base from where start building up more and more features.Contributions to the code are more than welcome! Also, if you find any bug, don't hesitate in opening an issue on GitHub :)"]},
{"question": "Toolchains as Code", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "String Interning in Python | CPython Internals", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "React vs Vue: Which Framework to Choose in 2021?", "details": "", "answers": ["One thing these tick-a-box comparisons tend to not factor in is the long-term health of the codebase. I co-wrote and maintained a React frontend which grew to over 100k lines over 5 years. In that period the project moved from createClass -> Class components -> functional components, from JavaScript with Proptypes -> Flow -> TypeScript and from flux -> redux. Most of the time we were able to find codemods for upgrades, the only one I remember being difficult was going from flux to redux, every other change was trivial.I've never picked Vue for any project since, primarily because I've gotten the impression that a project is likelier than not to be stuck on the version that it started on."]},
{"question": "\"The World Is Your Green Screen\" v2, and also in Real-Time now", "details": "", "answers": ["Having done a little amateur rotoscoping before, the input here seems pretty happy path -- large white backgrounds or a great degree of contrast between the subject and background colors. It would be interesting to see how this holds up under a more complicated demo, such as a moving camera or a more dynamic background."]},
{"question": "An interview about the Luminaire project and how it simplifies the work of building anomaly detection projects for time series data.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Open Source code is great for marketing a business too!", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How U.S. agencies' trust in untested software opened the door to hackers", "details": "", "answers": ["I\u2019m surprised that there hasn\u2019t been more talk of open source as part of the solution. I think the issue I see is there\u2019s lots of manual checkboxes and audits and reviews and little that would have prevented this exploit. At least having an open source agent would allow for more types of automated sast scans. If it\u2019s not open source then it becomes pretty difficult to verify as a vendor can just say they do it and do it poorly."]},
{"question": "What does your tech stack look like based on the letters of your first name?", "details": "", "answers": [""]},
{"question": "From the Ground Up: How We Built the Nanos Unikernel", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "More challenging projects every programmer should try", "details": "", "answers": ["My first ever interview for a software development position opened with, \"What happens when you type Yelp.com into your web browser and press enter?\"I hate questions like this. Programming is such a broad field that you can be perfectly competent and have no idea how a browser works."]},
{"question": "Webspicy: An API specification and test framework that yields better coverage for less testing effort.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0631\u0646\u0627\u0645\u062c \u062c\u0648\u0645\u0644\u0627 \u0627\u062e\u0641\u0627\u0621 \u0628\u0639\u0636 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0635\u0627\u0626\u0635 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u0627\u0644\u0627\u062a | Joomla Setting indivi...", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "[self-promotion] Implementing Keyless Tables in our OSS Database", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Open sourced project for first time contributors", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "UNIX Recovery Legend, coming back from rm -rf *", "details": "", "answers": ["Impressive, honestly would have pulled the plug and tried mounting or dd out from another host. Always carry a screwdriver"]},
{"question": "Write code. Not too much. Mostly functions.", "details": "", "answers": ["Write what is simple, and natural, and human.Code, by very definition, is neither simple nor human."]},
{"question": "Docker in 10 minutes", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Automated Testing for Free!!", "details": "", "answers": ["Reminds me of , or maybe icontract-hypothesis depending on how you're handling preconditions.  Fun :-)"]},
{"question": "Be as harsh as you want this is my first page with web design and basic coding. I would just like some feedback and tips", "details": "", "answers": ["The drawn line appears to be some 20-50 pixels directly below where I point the mouse and hold the left mouse button.You use event.pageX and event.pageY for your drawing. Let's see the documentation for event.pageX:The pageX property returns the horizontal coordinate (according to the document) of the mouse pointer when a mouse event was triggered.The document is the web page.Aha, surely you want the co-ordinate relative to the canvas to which you attach the event?canvas.addEventListener('mousemove', draw);\n\nfunction draw(event) {\n  if (mouseDown){\n    drawLine(x1, y1, event.pageX, event.pageY);\n    x1 = event.pageX;\n    y1 = event.pageY;\n  }\n}\nPerhaps instead of pageX and pageY you're better off using offsetX and offsetY:The offsetX property returns the x-coordinate of the mouse pointer, relative to the target element.In paint.js:\n\n\n\n\n"]},
{"question": "\"I took FSF Europe to court.\"", "details": "", "answers": ["What a username."]},
{"question": "Python without significant whitespace", "details": "", "answers": ["maybe add a readme?"]},
{"question": "Fast , simple, low HTTP router and URL matcher for building Deno servers \ud83e\udd95.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "reader \u2013 a Python library to create your own RSS feed reader", "details": "", "answers": ["Awesome! What makes this library better than something like ? I use this in a current project of mine, and might want to look into trying something else."]},
{"question": "Released RustFFT 5.0.0-experimental.1: Now faster than FFTW!", "details": "", "answers": ["does anyone know what is FFT use for in industry setting, I remember learning about it in control class back in college, but don't remember much."]},
{"question": "What they are and what they say they are are two different things", "details": "", "answers": ["If you have something to say about this as it relates specifically to programming I'd like to hear it. \nOtherwise you're posting in the wrong sub."]},
{"question": "A lecture on computational model programmed to simulate biological process of DNA compaction", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0631\u0646\u0627\u0645\u062c \u062c\u0648\u0645\u0644\u0627 \u0627\u062e\u0641\u0627\u0621 \u0628\u0639\u0636 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0635\u0627\u0626\u0635 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0642\u0627\u0644\u0627\u062a | Joomla Setting indivi...", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "(AI code generator) The concept is to upload design docs, annotate, and then receive your dynamic front end code on the other side via an ANN. How would this be used in large engineering organizations, based on the way you currently do things?", "details": "", "answers": ["Honestly? It wouldn't.We might try it out as an experiment, and then we'd measure how much time it takes to fix up the mistakes in the generation compared to the time it saved.Then, like every time, we would find it was a net loss in productivity. If it was the best one we'd seen so far it would be documented that anyone needs to make a cookie cutter content spammer site or some other simple out-of-the-box type of site, this one might be a good choice."]},
{"question": "Javascript tools for Animation", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Read a paper: Cross-language interoperability using Truffle and Graal", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "C++ fast logging library", "details": "", "answers": ["Fast wrt ? BoostLog? Spdlog?"]},
{"question": "EdivaldoDomingos/Training-coding-skills-and-knowledge", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0631\u0646\u0627\u0645\u062c \u062c\u0648\u0645\u0644\u0627 [ \u062a\u0639\u0631\u064a\u0641 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0648\u062f\u064a\u0648\u0644 ] | Joomla Configure Modules", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "A different way to reverse an array", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "\ud83d\udcd710+ Noteworthy Bootstrap Admin Themes Made With the Latest Version of Vue", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Researchers have developed a deep learning-based algorithm to detect anomalies in time series data. The technology could provide advance warning of potential failures in systems ranging from satellites to computer data centers.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "CPython Optimizations - String Interning", "details": "", "answers": ["So now there are lots of strings but you don't have to pay for most of them because they are interns. Just don't tell HR."]},
{"question": "Conan O'Brien and guests saying \"You know?\" a hundred times in one minute - Speech Analysis", "details": "", "answers": ["You can find how it was made + the GitHub link in "]},
{"question": "A quick opensource tool to build 3D models from the voxels or 2D layers.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "4 misconceptions in machine learning | ML relality - ucompare.in", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Dasel v1.10 released. You can now query, update and convert between data formats, insert documents of any format into others, additional selectors and more.", "details": "", "answers": ["Cool! How hard would it be to develop a language plugin? This would be great for some company specific tooling"]},
{"question": "Monica Lent: Progress Is More Important Than Perfection | Maintainable", "details": "", "answers": ["This is similar to the . Also, it . Web start-ups are generally better off being nimble than accurate to gain market share faster than competitors, but banking software needs more attention because losing people's money will produce lots of lawsuits and maybe loss of banking license, and astronaut life-support systems need very careful scrutiny for hopefully obvious reasons.I've seen design mistakes where somebody used to one domain transferred to another and either over or under focused on perfection out of habit. Know your domain, and if you don't, learn from those who do.I used early Amazon, and it was buggy as heck. But I kept using it because it had more product choice than the alternatives such that I lived with some bugs. But I did avoid ordering anything expensive. However, the high end was not Amazon's forte back then, perhaps for a reason.Microsoft has left some silly bugs in its products for a long time because they have/had insufficient competition to bother. This is a common problem with oligopolies and monopolies."]},
{"question": "SerenityOS got pwned at hxp CTF 2020! Significantly harder than last year but they still got us :) Full exploit and writeup", "details": "", "answers": ["Hello friends! I was super happy to learn that SerenityOS had been featured again in this year's hxp CTF.After seeing how easily we fell to last year's CTF, I became interested in OS security and have done a large amount of work on SerenityOS to beef up its defenses. Many others have contributed great work towards this as well.It was very nice to hear from the hxp challenge organizer that we were a significantly more difficult target this year. And of course, now we need to make it even harder for them next year!If you're interested, I made .Thanks for visiting my thread, and have a great day!Edit: Since I have your attention, let me also plug  :)"]},
{"question": "Unit Tests vs Integration Tests - Which is Better?", "details": "", "answers": ["The one that is written."]},
{"question": "Making a RISC-V Operating System in Rust", "details": "", "answers": ["Does RISC-V being an ISA include components like [SV39] MMU, or does the author simply pair the one with the other for convenience and to be able to actually test a computer -- I imagine a CPU alone cannot run an OS, much less one that uses paging?"]},
{"question": "Half-Precision Floating-Point, Visualized", "details": "", "answers": ["Nice article :)How come the choice was to implement 2047 NaNs and not use these values for something else? Is there an advantage I can't see? Thanks!"]},
{"question": "Data Science in Python Programming", "details": "", "answers": ["From the conclusion:Python is a powerful programming language. That is why there is little to no chance that Python programming will affect the data science system.So you're saying that Python won't have any impact on the \"data science system\"? Yet the article itself praises Python and says that it's the best language for data science."]},
{"question": "Website Ideas To Practice Your Web Development Skills", "details": "", "answers": ["Linked article says \"Posted on 10 June, 2018\". Might still have useful ideas."]},
{"question": "Made a script to give my server a couple of animated eyes, the goal is to based the animation on metrics of the system (cpu, ram, disk). Feel free to collaborate. Any help would be appreciated", "details": "", "answers": ["So concerned eyes for warnings,  angry eyes for disk space, Forgetful for memory alarms or thoughtful eyes for intense cpu usage,  straight up crazy eyes when the errors roll in?"]},
{"question": "programming beginner journey", "details": "", "answers": ["I have no clue how reddit works anyways yea i jus started python and want a project idea to challenge myself. any suggestions for a beginner ? 4 hrs of coding experience so far :)"]},
{"question": "The web is 30 years old today", "details": "", "answers": ["I don't see December 12th, 1990 as a particular date in the history of the WWW Project: Maybe it was the date of the first demo on \"Christmas\" 1990? One could just as well use March 1989 (first written proposal) or August 1991 (public release) for the birth date of the web..."]},
{"question": "ThreeJS Xmas Crystal Balls with 360 ESA Panorama", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Ansible Basics | Ansible Playbook Tutorial For Beginners | Automate Folder Creation And File Copy", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Noton: Compute by drawing cables (Inspired by paper computing)", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Data Fetching with React Server Components", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Porgramming a Popular Half-Life Mod During the Rise of Counter-Strike", "details": "", "answers": ["Seeing that hammer editor again was a great throwback.  Thanks for that! Sadly I don't think I have anything of the old stuff I did back then anymore. Would have been nice to see that again :/"]},
{"question": "Get up to speed with partial clone and shallow clone - The GitHub Blog", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "A Year of 379 Computer Days: December Added", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to measure software project complexity objectively", "details": "", "answers": ["There are many ways of estimating software complexity - none perfect, but many good as rule-of-thumb. The most comprehensive treatment I know of is Stutzke \"Estimating Software-Intensive Systems\", which considers a variety of formulaic models and also discusses the human factors."]},
{"question": "How to add setuptools-scm to your package | A small improvement for lazy developers", "details": "", "answers": ["I've been using this for years and it's an amazing difference if you want to automate yours deploys and make sure you don't screw them up.Especially if you auto-deploy from git tags.Without this, you need to manually specify a version number on TWO places manually, which is both duplicate works and a mistake waiting to happen."]},
{"question": "Is Ruby 3 Actually Three Times Faster?", "details": "", "answers": ["I think they really messed up the messaging around Ruby 3. Looking at what it contains, it seems like starting a new era of Ruby with some new foundational things that won't see maturity until later versions. But the messaging is comparing it to Ruby 2 and looking backwards. Particularly by comparing to Ruby 2.0, they've created a situation where people are a bit disappointed as a lot of the performance gains have already been had working up to Ruby 2.7.Still, just a messaging issue. Great work and looking forward to seeing the features mature in future versions."]},
{"question": "OpenAPI Generator v5.0.0 released with new generators, refactored clients and more", "details": "", "answers": ["We're currently using it at my company. Is there a complete Changelog? It feels a bit weird to just scroll around in the PRs."]},
{"question": "jitboy: A Game Boy emulator with dynamic recompilation (JIT) for x86-64", "details": "", "answers": ["Cool project. The way the README is written sounds like somebody's thesis."]},
{"question": "How we built the GitHub globe", "details": "", "answers": ["lol at them building the exact same thing as  ....and no citation"]},
{"question": "Effort estimation \u2014 it\u2019s complicated: On the dilemma of evaluating software development effort", "details": "", "answers": ["Estimation is hard because programming isn't intuitive. If you are building a house, you can estimate that building two houses will take approximately twice the man hours. With programming, you might be able to instantly copy the first house. Also with programming, seemingly minor changes to details might be extremely hard. So you want a different color light bulb? Intuitively you know this is a trip to lowes and a five minute task. But if you're programming, depending on the codebase this might involve changing the color of every light bulb or maybe rewiring the whole house. The only way to give a good estimate is to know the codebase well enough to understand how the feature will be implemented and also make sure the people asking for the feature also understand exactly what they are asking for. Any change that is too complicated to envision the final implementation of, including many seemingly insignificant details, is going to be impossible to estimate properly. For example, I want to make my node.js app use https. This can be accomplished by changing a single line from require(http) to require(https), but then to do it properly, it turns out I need to understand certificate creation, and then certificate installation, and then handling certificate expiration, and certificate distribution, and hostname matching and modifying the hosts file and how to get node.js to recognize the windows certificate store, and how to detect and request elevation during certificate installation. How would it be possible to give a decent estimate if you haven't done this before? If you have done it before then the estimate is drastically different because you already know all the steps and may already have automated most of them. So really the answer for estimates is either: 1 day (I've already done it before and just need to refresh myself and add the feature) or I have no idea."]},
{"question": "Most Popular Programming Languages", "details": "", "answers": ["I've checked your profile. Why do you spam your articles on subs that are totally unrelated to them (at example, )?"]},
{"question": "How Envoy is using Security Scorecards to improve its external dependency policy", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Earable Computing: The Research team believes that earphones will be the next significant milestone in wearable devices and that new hardware, software, and apps will all run on this platform.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Corrupt Latin: How Orthography Revealed Corruption in Kyrgyzstan - bellingcat", "details": "", "answers": ["Interesting topic, but this code, and the way that it's presented in images, with the comments completely out of line in separate bullet points, is a bit unusual and tedious to follow."]},
{"question": "Array & Linked List - described with cats in a box.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "The Dependency Jungle", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Quine or self reproducing program written using C language", "details": "", "answers": [" is still an interesting read if you find this concept interesting."]},
{"question": "how to make an encrypter and decrypter in python", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Batch Processing Massive Data Much Quicker with TiSpark", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to get into the dream company. Preparation tips. - ucompare.in", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Top 8 Open Source Headless CMS 2020", "details": "", "answers": ["404"]},
{"question": "Designing a better terminal", "details": "", "answers": ["Obviously, a fresh set of eyes looking at a problem is always a good thing, and I'd never begrudge anybody for making something they find useful.  And I do my best to differentiate 'this isn't targeted at me' from 'this is bad.'But, uh, at very least this clearly isn't targeted at me.Easy access to the servers you usually log intoThere is an underlying mental model here that connections should be a first class citizen in the UI because a terminal is \"a way of connecting to servers\" that doesn't make a ton of sense to me.  As soon as you are responsible for 10,000 servers, many of which are ephemeral VM's, this sort of UI and mental model breaks down.  It also breaks down when the majority of your terminal sessions are expected to be local.  It also breaks when you want to connect to servers in different ways.  ssh'ing as a different user, or with a different DISPLAY environment variable set before invoking ssh apparently requires reconfiguring a preset rather than just running DISPLAY=:1 ssh otheruser@server instead of ssh server  Also, having multiple tabs connected to one server is non obvious with this UI.Integrated docs so you don\u2019t have to search the webUh, man page?  I am confused by the premise that I don't have access to docs in a terminal to start with.  You can subdivide a good existing terminal emulator into multiple panes already if you don't want your man page in a different tab or window.  Or use a tiling window manager so another terminal window is the same thing as another pane in this terminal window.you can then click on the commands and they instantly copy into your terminal cursor.That sounds horrific to do by accident.  And I can already select something and middle-click in the terminal in X11 without needing to reinvent the terminal.  One extra click seems much safer, and not significantly harder.  And standard X11 selection copying works in all my apps, not just a reimagined terminal.The password manager is in the terminal!Uh, okay.  Again, not sure why the terminal emulator is the thing here.  Just set git or whatever to cache you passwords and it works in every terminal emulator, or like with man pages just run some program in another pane instead of making it a terminal feature.Running 6 servers like I do, I probably have about 20 passwords per server. That\u2019s 120 passwordsDafuq?  Set up keys or join these servers to a domain.  Having this problem makes no sense in the first place.  Hey look, I made some beautiful embroidered covers I can put over the grody bullet wounds from where I keep shooting myself.  Isn't it a great solution?!History is always availableOther terminal emulators like iTerm have the sidebar feature.  And history | grep whatever is right there...So, if you find this sort of thing useful, go nuts.  But I gotta admit I'm not understanding the unique benefits here.  The click-to copy in the terminal's password manager actually was kinda neat.  A generic Protocol for a 'copy' button actually would be pretty neat."]},
{"question": "Python Programming Machine Learning Tutorials You Can Look For", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Road to 1.0/ Zig", "details": "", "answers": ["Old but still important IMO. Especially as Zig has developed a lot and it's pretty good now"]},
{"question": "Turbo - The speed of a single-page web application without having to write any JavaScript. Open sourced by Basecamp", "details": "", "answers": ["Sounds... Slow"]},
{"question": "Wow Internet Cuantico!? Hacia donde vamos...", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Instagram Phosway: Networks without Barriers (NWxB)", "details": "", "answers": ["What is the why behind all of this? I'm not sure about the goal of the project"]},
{"question": "Free Intro to AI/ML Course for Beginners", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "From Balenciaga to Basics: Lessons from Our Pivot to API Tooling", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Top 10 Most Popular Programming Languages in 2021", "details": "", "answers": ["Top AD 10 AD Most AD Popular AD AD AD AD barf.Wow. I didn\u2019t realize what a spammer this user is."]},
{"question": "The flaws in the new UK & EU regulation for tech companies", "details": "", "answers": ["TL:DR: a lot of preening by a consultancy in an effort to show how smart they are, with almost nothing of substance said about the ostensible subject."]},
{"question": "App Store Connect holiday schedule - News", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Read JSON file in Python", "details": "", "answers": ["The ujson package has basically the same API as import json but is ~4 times faster (circa 2015) - handy if you need to read larger datasets, otherwise the default json package takes too long."]},
{"question": "Useful animation library for your project", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Yule Special", "details": "", "answers": ["Posted a while ago the teaser for this episode. It is finally out!ABSTRACT:\u201cCode like there is no tomorrow\u201d.2020 has been a difficult year for most of us but some good things did happen. We have gathered the lineup of the Book Club Season One to review what were the good things that happened this year, what were the bad things and how can software change the world in which we are living for the better. Join Martin Fowler, Richard Feldman, Mike Amundsen, Dave Thomas, Erik Sch\u00f6n, Sa\u0161a Juri\u0107, Casey Rosenthal, Andy Hunt and Aino Vonge Corry as they set out to highlight their year in review and draw some main learnings."]},
{"question": "How To Make a Text to Binary Translator - Python", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Dbxfs: Open-source Dropbox client runs natively on M1 Macs", "details": "", "answers": ["its in python lol?"]},
{"question": "Show HN: Django and React SaaS boilerplate tutorial", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Software Architecture is overrated. Questions and feedback are welcome, what's your experience?", "details": "", "answers": ["I currently am employed as a software architect, and IMO the problem is not that software architecture is overrated, is that people overestimate the real functionality of what they are designing. For example, most recently I have helped plan and build a subscription based billing platform to which the business expects will run > 6 million transactions annually. Personally, I believe it won\u2019t even be close to that, as they have 0 subscribers. As a result the application was likely wildly overbuilt for the MVP release, but I could very well be wrong in my thought. Long story short, architecture matters more from the standpoint of strategy and understanding usage as well as production environment. Where architecture goes wrong is the notion that your application is infallible and should survive for more that 10 years, rather than building something that will do the job with a margin of runway and a plan for expansion/evolution. Modern software moves too quickly to think things won\u2019t need to be radically updated with the times."]},
{"question": "Programming Languages for Data Science", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Help me code something cool", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "The Most Popular Programming Languages - 1965/2020 - Statistics and Data", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Creating a Distributable Game with Python Tutorial (under 200 lines of code)", "details": "", "answers": ["I\u2019d recommend creating python packages if you wish to distribute this.  Also it\u2019s just good practice, and sets you up for unit testing. Also, pyenv is a useful tool to use when coding python.  Mac\u2019s system python and brews python is not as flexible."]},
{"question": "Coding challenges", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "The architecture of IMGZ", "details": "", "answers": ["I guess this is meme \ud83d\ude00"]},
{"question": "A star Path finding in Python", "details": "", "answers": ["This video is tight!\ud83d\ude06\ud83d\ude0d"]},
{"question": "Filling the void of a physical whiteboard", "details": "", "answers": ["I've started using Mermaid/PlantUML-esque tools more and more since the whole lockdown thing, and honestly, they've been super useful to me. I show some code examples in the article and talk about how I sort of try and use it to replace a whiteboard in my working process."]},
{"question": "Compile 1 Million Lines Of C++ In ~2 Minutes With A 16 Core Ryzen 9 5950x", "details": "", "answers": ["News flash: Using more cores of your multi-core CPU reduces build times!:eyeroll:I love how a shitty, bug-ridden development environment that costs  still requires you to buy a separate  to enable parallel builds, a standard feature available on practically every other closed and open source compiler and build system out of the box for $0 extra."]},
{"question": "HTML Over The Wire", "details": "", "answers": ["I've  played around with Stimulus a decent amount, and found it to be a good experience. Especially when combined with all of Rails existing builtin form tools. I'm a fan of this approach, and I think a huge number of sites would benefit from moving away from \"everything needs to be a SPA\".People are going to make fun of this because it's an \"everything old is new again\" thing, while missing that Basecamp is pushing this stuff because it turns out a lot of the old ideas were actually good, but just needed better tooling."]},
{"question": "Visa - Easy third party authentication (OAuth 2.0) for flutter apps. Merry Christmas!!", "details": "", "answers": ["Cool library, but I'm pretty sure that the name \"Visa\" already has a well established meaning in the online payments space ;)"]},
{"question": "React Server Components", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Why to Learn Python", "details": "", "answers": ["tl;dr: chase the latest fadsPython is in-demand. This is the foremost reason for why to learn python."]},
{"question": "Document-oriented, embedded SQL database for Go, works with Bolt, Badger and memory", "details": "", "answers": ["What does this do better than current offerings"]},
{"question": "What is an SDK? [Simple Guide to Software Development Kits]", "details": "", "answers": ["It's a red flag that some software is  too complex / opinionated / proprietary to bother learning:\n\n\n\n"]},
{"question": "Git Koans", "details": "", "answers": ["And where are they? O.o"]},
{"question": "Hlo everyone, I want to start with programming and become a game developer. Can any one help me out plz.. I am thinking of starting with html and CSS with the below book. If someone feels I am doing wrong or I should be doing something else, plz let me know in comments. Thnks \ud83e\udd17", "details": "", "answers": ["Dont wanna be rude, but if you can\u2018t even lookup which languages you need to use for game developement and come up with web developement as a result, then good luck learning programming."]},
{"question": "3 Things to Know Before Rethinking Your Engineering Interview Process", "details": "", "answers": ["Our desired talents are recurring patterns of thought, feeling, and behavior that can be productively applied in the context of Lyft\u2019s ML SWE role. What we\u2019re looking for here is a bit more complicated than simply work done in the past by a candidate. Faced with the same stimuli, people react and behave differently. When we look for role and values fit, we do mean just that. Beyond skills and knowledge, will a candidate\u2019s unique way of responding to the problems thrown up in Lyft\u2019s business context help that candidate succeed? So while conventional wisdom might suggest it, we\u2019re not always looking for the Michael Jordans of machine learning (be it I. or J.). The narrow sort of talents associated with celebrated excellence can be important but in most cases the interviewers are listening for predictive clues of how a candidate will react when posed Lyft-specific problems on the job.What a pretentious and pompous way of saying that there's more to hiring than just hiring \"rockstars\" (I hate that term), that your hiring process should consist of giving candidates problems similar to what you deal with (you'd think this one is obvious) and that different people think differently (gasp! shock!)."]},
{"question": "Upgrading DevTools' architecture to the modern web", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "An experimental text editor based on Scintilla and Turbo Vision", "details": "", "answers": ["YES! this is the sort of thing I've been hoping someone would do for a while. We seemed to crack terminal UI's in the 90's and then weirdly backtrack for some reason but this is just so easy to use that its basically impossible to be confused. There should definitely be a terminal text editor like this in common use.Obviously its not 100% there yet (for one thing it seems to be stuck spinning at 100% cpu all the time on OSX) but I'm going to keep an eye on this one for sure."]},
{"question": "Hotwire: An alternative approach to building modern web applications without using much JavaScript by sending HTML instead of JSON over the wire.", "details": "", "answers": ["Time is a flat circle"]},
{"question": "make scrapy a very simple distributed & high-performance easily", "details": "", "answers": ["Learn to write."]},
{"question": "Going All In on the Mac App Store", "details": "", "answers": ["Nice post, I think it explains the rationale well!One unrelated suggestion: perhaps make it easier to find out what your product actually is from the website. I tried to click everywhere to go to the home page to find out more, but couldn\u2019t manage."]},
{"question": "Does C have a runtime ?", "details": "", "answers": ["Yes."]},
{"question": "iOS versioning: build number", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "I made a program in Excel that automates youtube-dl, and I'm very proud of it! All you have to do is paste your link(s), choose download location, and click a button!!", "details": "", "answers": ["I made a program that automates youtube-dl, too! I wrote it in python. It's kind of like flexget for youtube. You can set it up to run periodically with cron or a scheduled task. It uses a yaml file with rss urls of youtube channels, the directory to download each channel into and optional filters so you only download the videos you want. You can setup an rss feed of your own using something like TTRSS then share videos you want downloaded into a feed that the automated script watches. And if you don't know the RSS feed of a youtube channel you can use the -r flag and the path to the main channel and the script will return it so you can put it into your yaml file."]},
{"question": "Try this handy and free-to-use IDE", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Hello I am new to programming and I would like to learn programming Android applications, and I decided to learn the Java But I don't know exactly where to start What do you advise me?", "details": "", "answers": ["Imo if you want to learn Android you should consider learning Kotlin instead of Java because it's has been the recommended language for Android by Google for some time now. Telling you where to start is hard. I learned programming by buying an introductory Java book and working through it but it really depends on what kind of learner you are."]},
{"question": "the art of selling a tiny IT project", "details": "", "answers": ["Well you seen one guy do this and spun a useless article from it? Like no personality or feel of being involved in the problem your portraying as your experience.Your references work for any selling process than you affiliate scammy posture products.."]},
{"question": "5 Best Examples of UX Design in Real World", "details": "", "answers": ["Is this a joke? Site has things popping up and obsuring the web page every few seconds."]},
{"question": "Tutorial video explaining Paging in x86_64 systems and how to add it to your C++ OS", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How To Write Cover Letter To Get More Interview Invites Than Ever (For Software Engineers)", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Mind answering this poll I made?", "details": "", "answers": ["Read the sub rules."]},
{"question": "AI Practitioner vs AI Developer", "details": "", "answers": ["this should be blog not video, since it shows text  notes and no speech included"]},
{"question": "A modern port of Turbo Vision 2.0", "details": "", "answers": ["wow very impressive, congrats!would you please provide it as a Portable App to make it easier to consume?"]},
{"question": "just wanted to share a little program I made in python", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Retired Microsoft engineer Dave Plummer talks about hunting bugs in task manager and space cadet pinball", "details": "", "answers": ["Do they talk about why they removed pinball anyway? I heard there were some issues wth the code."]},
{"question": "Free Fullstack Development Foundations Program", "details": "", "answers": ["\n\n\n\n\n\nThe rigorous curriculum will help you to understand all the intermediary based concepts of full stack programming. You will learn the most happening technologies like HTML, CSS and JavaScript which will enable you to develop a fully functional web application.We understand your requirements, hence the program curriculum has been designed by top industry experts. The program will cover all the ABCs essential for a beginner and a professional as well. The program involves\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n09/01/2021 - Orientation, Live Class, Coding Challenge10/01/2021 - Live Class, Assignment, Interview Questions16/01/2021 - Live Coding Project 1- Part 1, Assignment17/01/2021 - Live Coding Project 1 - Part 2, Project 2 Introduction, Interview questions 8:30 am - 12:30 pm EST & 7 pm - 11 pm ISTThe candy crush game clone will be the practical execution of all the concepts covered in the program. It will be a guided project done during a live coding class. The project covers the design and development that includes HTML page creation and CSS animations with the power-packed JavaScript code to make the application super functional.By the start of this project, you will be capable and experienced to develop your clone of the \u2018color flood\u2019 game. This project will be done individually giving you complete freedom to express your creativity and approach in terms of coding."]},
{"question": "HalMakeBeep - Reversing A Tiny Built-In Windows Kernel Module [Journey from Kernel32 to HAL]", "details": "", "answers": ["Makes me wonder how it's done now. XP was the last OS to use the PC speaker. Later versions now emulate this via Soundcard."]},
{"question": "DirectX creator Eric Engstrom dies aged 55, leaving behind a game-changing legacy", "details": "", "answers": ["According to wikipedia, he died from complications from dropping a monitor on his foot. Talk about unlucky. Damn."]},
{"question": "Jepsen: Scylla 4.2-rc3", "details": "", "answers": ["I love these write ups. The last time I discussed Jepsen with my father, he wondered if it would be reasonable for testing Tandem Nonstop SQL (he worked on that)."]},
{"question": "KataScript v0.1 - Initial Release", "details": "", "answers": ["A couple weeks ago I posted about accidentally creating a scripting language In the time since, I've been using KataScript for game scripts, added a lot of features, found and fixed a lot of bugs, and added unit tests.Now, KataScript is relatively robust and fully featured, so it's time for a v0.1 release!language overview: live interpreter: "]},
{"question": "Expert Guide to IntelliJ License Server", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Using Monokai? Now you can wear it.", "details": "", "answers": ["Is it actually the exact Monokai colors?"]},
{"question": "How Bad Is Your Spotify? A sophisticated A.I. judges your awful taste in music.", "details": "", "answers": ["My Spotify keeps suggesting crappy music to begin with. I didn't need an AI to tell me that"]},
{"question": "Question: How does git detect renames?", "details": "", "answers": ["It ain't pretty: "]},
{"question": "Self-hosting Kubernetes on your Raspberry Pi", "details": "", "answers": ["\"And if the idea of self-hosting something turns you off, then stop reading now and post a derisive comment on Hacker News\":)"]},
{"question": "Like Growing Fruits: The Reality of Multi-Tenancy", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Here's a list of Free/Open Source Software I made; comment in any suggestions you may have. Thank you! Happy Holidays!", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Now in Android: 31 - Modern Android development, AndroidX, articles, and more!", "details": "", "answers": ["\u201cModern\u201d Android development. You can\u2019t polish a turd."]},
{"question": "Code comments are your code autobiography: The importance (and benefits) of writing code comments as part of implementing your code [Unpopular opinion].", "details": "", "answers": ["In my experience, it takes a few decades of reading code to appreciate that every extra hint of the intention of the original programmer, including stale comments, is useful..."]},
{"question": "I created a Visualization of 20 Sorting Algorithms as a Christmas Tree with Java. Merry Xmas :)", "details": "", "answers": ["These are always fun. I want to do something like this, but I have no idea how to do the visuals."]},
{"question": "Best Ways to Learn How to Code", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to Learn Python Programming", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "We rendered a million web pages to find out what makes the web slow", "details": "", "answers": ["firing up 200 EC2 instances, rendering a million web pages over the weekend, Definitely skipping over the hardest part here"]},
{"question": "[Cheat Sheet ] JavaScript Object Functions Part 1", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to Favicon in 2021: Six files that fit most needs", "details": "", "answers": ["Doesn't this article just kind of assume your site is a PWA? Maybe I glossed over something, but it seemed like it."]},
{"question": "Making a typeracer bot that types over 400 WPM", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Userscripts Are Fun And Are Still Very Much Relevant", "details": "", "answers": [". Still a lot easier than making an extension."]},
{"question": "Conan O'Brien saying \"You know?\" 100 times in 1 minute - Speech Analysis project", "details": "", "answers": ["\"You\"  :shakes zucchini: \"know\""]},
{"question": "Release 2.0.0 (2020-12-21) \u00b7 timescale/timescaledb", "details": "", "answers": ["PostgreSQL for time\u2011seriesTimescaleDB is the leading open-source relational database for time-series data. Fully managed or self\u2011hosted."]},
{"question": "Switching from Apple to Lenovo", "details": "", "answers": ["I mean if you don\u2019t use an OS for years... yea you\u2019re going to have some problems adjusting. Also Windows isn\u2019t a Unix like OS so development has its own learning curve. As for Windows pestering telemetry notifications those can be muted along with all of the other pop ups. Idk. This reads like someone who just doesn\u2019t like working with Windows. I use a Mac, a Lenovo with Ubuntu, and a desktop with Windows. I have reset the OS on all three machines more than once due to bloated cache and messy file systems from trial and error"]},
{"question": "What is AI Practitioner", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "GitHub Game Off 2020 - 500+ games with source code available", "details": "", "answers": ["Godot and GDscript has come a long way!"]},
{"question": "Inside story on fighting Uber's engineering disaster", "details": "", "answers": ["\n\n\n\nThese were resolved in two ways:\n\n-Osize\nThen the last two tweets are more-or-less \"\". Comes out of nowhere as the previous ~100 were about \"\" presented explicitly as all-or-nothing affairs not optimizing trade-off's."]},
{"question": "How to Host Your Modern Open-Source Web App for Free", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Introduction to Kali Linux - Best Linux Distro for Pentesting", "details": "", "answers": ["is there really that much difference in available ( actually available, not restricted to pre-installed stuff ) tools?"]},
{"question": "FreeBSD src 5ef5f51d2: Mark the repository has been converted to Git; This is the first Git commit to src.", "details": "", "answers": ["After 10 years, bazaar and CVS will be dead in the open source world. Mrcurial was removed from bitbucket this year, and it seems no one gives a fuck about SVN."]},
{"question": "Lovebyte2021 Invitro (512 bytes for TIC-80)", "details": "", "answers": ["visit party page : online version : youtube capture : "]},
{"question": "Samsung One UI 3.0 features and eligible devices launce date", "details": "", "answers": ["Not even close to what the sub is for"]},
{"question": "BlocklySQL - a block-based editor for SQL", "details": "", "answers": ["While I'm sure a lot of work went into this, I thought the idea of visual languages was to simplify stuff. :-)"]},
{"question": "How to Make the Fibonacci Sequence - Python", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Can anyone explain what \u201ccheckid_immediate\u201d and x-has-session is for OpenID in terms of privacy implications generally? (Link to question)", "details": "", "answers": [""]},
{"question": "Question I had that I figured I would post a link to here", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to import SFML C++ Project into is::Engine", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "My year in review (This aged really well):", "details": "", "answers": ["Which episode is that from?"]},
{"question": "AdditronK8S: A retrogames kubernetes controller built in Javascript", "details": "", "answers": ["Author here. I've created this project as a PoC for an internal talk of my company, it uses Dosbox + noVNC + a combination of tools to transport pulseaudio sounds to the browser and k3s+skaffold+javascript to implement the business logic.Feel free to ask me anything, happy holidays."]},
{"question": "Machine Learning Overview: Models, Algorithm and Learning Explained", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Top 3 sites that provide you with thousands of free professional programming books", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "To the brain, reading computer code is not the same as reading language", "details": "", "answers": ["Didnt someone post this exact article last week?"]},
{"question": "Making my own Alexa EP.1 | Building the Software Using Python", "details": "", "answers": ["Source?"]},
{"question": "Chaos vs. Python on Fibonacci \u00b7 The Chaos Programming Language", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Python Programming for Beginners \u2013 Every Code line Explained", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "C Is Not a Low-level Language", "details": "", "answers": ["So, that was an interesting take on the topic. You can apply the same arguments to any programming language on currently prevalent architectures, including assembly on x86.  While assembly offers a bunch of instructions that are closer to metal, isn't the reality that x86 has under the hood been a completely different architecture since about Pentium II?Assembly itself is at this point not much different from LLVM IR (or CIL or Java byte code, though those are much simpler). A representation that can be converted to various chips' real under the hood language, though that process is proprietary and covered under many layers of industrial secrets.You couldn't develop in a low-level language on x86 even if you wanted because x86 isn't metal. It's a specification of behaviors and capabilities, just like the C and C++ standards."]},
{"question": "Publish Source Link NuGet Packages with Azure Pipelines", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to Learn Python Coding?", "details": "", "answers": ["This website is the worst\n- it wants to show notifications\n- has a chatbox box\n- has a call us box\n- has a modal popup\n- has a popup banner\n- the footer at the bottom is an entire page length of links\n- looks like it was written by a copywriter just copy and pasting content from other sites"]},
{"question": "I wired my christmas tree with 500 LED lights and calculated their 3D coordinates", "details": "", "answers": ["Great and detailed video!Of course, now there's the obligatory next step.  Playing tetris (or snake) on your Christmas tree!"]},
{"question": "Google Discloses Poorly-Patched, Now Unpatched, Windows 0-Day Bug", "details": "", "answers": ["Windows print spooler API\u00a0Of course it's fucking printers."]},
{"question": "Top 10 Highest Paying Technologies To Learn In 2021", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Global Market Insights predicts that cloud providers will handle more data storage by 2025.", "details": "", "answers": ["Your weekly reminder that somewhere, someone actually paid real money for this study."]},
{"question": "5 Ways to install Node.js in a development machine", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "css custom scrollbar", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Simple database: should I create an API or just a javascript file with an object?", "details": "", "answers": ["Do you just want to store some persistent data? Or do you want to store data so multiple clients can access it?If it\u2019s the former then you don\u2019t need a database at all, just use Cookies.If it\u2019s the latter then the comment on the original post may help."]},
{"question": "5 Ways to install Node.js", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "World's First Smartphone with Under the Display Camera 5G", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Drawings animated by your current time of day and the season, using a 3D engine", "details": "", "answers": ["all hand made, this is pretty neat!"]},
{"question": "Top 10 Highest Paying Technologies To Learn In 2021", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Sort even number in ascending order and odd number in descending order in C++", "details": "", "answers": ["Both solutions look a bit convoluted, I probably would have done something like this:std::sort(vec.begin(), vec.end(),\n    [](int left, int right) {\n        if (left % 2) {\n            if (right % 2)\n                return left > right; // odd numbers sorted descending\n            else\n                return true; // odd numbers to the left\n        } else {\n            if (right % 2)\n                return false; // odd numbers to the left\n            else\n                return left < right; // even numbers sorted ascending\n        }\n    });\nNo fancy tricks and just the requirements turned into code. Also uses the more standard modulo for oddness checking. And it should also work with negative numbers."]},
{"question": "Microsoft Warns CrowdStrike of Hackers Targeting Azure Cloud Customers", "details": "", "answers": ["Not sure what this has to do with programming?"]},
{"question": "Beginner\u2019s guide to ARM programming with Microcontrollers (using STM32)", "details": "", "answers": ["This popped up on youtube for me yesterday!! Awesome video man. Thank you!!"]},
{"question": "A Complete Guide to LLVM for Programming Language Creators (diagrams + code)", "details": "", "answers": ["Author here. Let me know if you have any feedback! Have any of you used LLVM for your own languages?"]},
{"question": "How to Learn Coding for Free?", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to Trace Linux System Calls in Production with Minimal Impact on Performance", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "JavaScript Object Functions Cheat Sheet Part 2", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Comprehensive Ruby 3.0 changelog", "details": "", "answers": ["The project goals statement:\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n"]},
{"question": "Original Xbox Architecture A Practical Analysis", "details": "", "answers": ["I wonder what caused Microsoft to move from familiar x86-based architecture used in \"classic\" XBox to a custom PowerPC-based one with XBox 360. Was it cost, or performance, or both?Does anybody here know?"]},
{"question": "GraalVM Offers COBOL Support", "details": "", "answers": ["The first question to pop up in my mind was, \"Why?\"The article answers it here,The role of polyglot (multi-language) programming is an aim of GraalVM, where developers can create interoperable software that is native compiled, connecting to a library from another language that provides a benefit but may not be understood by the author. In the case of COBOL, applications that are compiled with GnuCobol can be engaged by developers who understand Java. This bridge can help bridge the gap to maintain older software systems that may be written in COBOL but are difficult to maintain."]},
{"question": "JavaScript Object Functions cheat sheet Part 3", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Cyberpwned, an automatic solver for Cyberpunk's hacking minigame using OCR, available now on Android! Play Store approval is pending, but you can side-load the current release and take a look at the (horrible, messy) source code.", "details": "", "answers": ["Son of a bitch, he did it.I was reading through your thread discussing how you were contemplating doing this last week. Happy you went through with it and I wish you success.Edit: changed a word."]},
{"question": "CyberSecurity Telegram Channel powered by a BOT. With the recent state of data breaches. I created this Telegram Channel powered by a bot which will send news articles along with tips and tricks related to cybersecurity. No ads, no analytics. Just pure articles! https://t.me/cyber_security_feed", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Skew is a web-first, cross-platform programming language with an optimizing compiler.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to make a Third Person Game - Camera & Movements | C++ 3D Game Tutorial Series - Part 26", "details": "", "answers": ["The source code is available at the following address:  "]},
{"question": "Diving into the deep code waters Tools and techniques for exploring an unknown (large) codebase", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "[Coming Soon] Self XDSD - Automated Management for Github Projects", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Linked List Cycle | Explained Python Solution | Leetcode", "details": "", "answers": ["Tips and Comments appreciated thanks."]},
{"question": "Anyone know good books about programming?", "details": "", "answers": ["For a beginner I\u2019d recommend Learn Python the Hard Way. By Zed Shaw. You\u2019ll need some extra exercises to master it I\u2019m 2/3rds of the way through at the moment."]},
{"question": "List of Beginner level projects in C++ to learn programming", "details": "", "answers": ["Nothing is more pro than conio.h and turbo C++."]},
{"question": "Ruby 3 Released", "details": "", "answers": ["I love Ruby! I use it mostly for shell stuff. It's great not limiting myself to Bash and Zsh intricacies."]},
{"question": "Developer and Power Users Tool List for Windows", "details": "", "answers": ["Everything is the best software I ever used. It's one of very few things I miss when I'm on Linux."]},
{"question": "10 KB Club: A curated collection of interesting websites whose home pages do not exceed 10 KB compressed size", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "What comes after Git? It's been 15 years since it was created. SVN was created 5 years before Git. CVS was 15 years before SVN", "details": "", "answers": ["The answer to this question can be found by asking another more pointed question: What problems exist in the VCS space that git isn't addressing?I think much of the innovation in this space hasn't been in VCSs directly, but around them. While git wasn't the first distributed version control system, it did help to make DVCS available outside of commercial products like BitKeeper. GitHub and their competitors took that to the next logical step by making it easy to host and share git repositories. The pull request system absolutely was innovative in that regard (whether Linus admits it or not), and it addressed a pain point for developers.Last thoughts here. It feels like we haven't seen a lot of innovation in languages or tooling in the last 10 years in general. We plateaued in that area because there hasn't been a need to improve. Instead we've seen it in infrastructure, which makes sense because that is where a lot of the pain in software development was. Containerization has been a game changer.Whatever comes next will be driven by pain and need."]},
{"question": "Dev-C++ Is a Low Memory Windows Native C++ IDE Built in Delphi", "details": "", "answers": ["That's a name I haven't heard in a long time."]},
{"question": "21 Super Fun and Cool Python Projects for Beginners", "details": "", "answers": ["How many of you guys enjoy working on projects which will be thrown out? I'm not big fan of it, but probably that is the only option sometimes"]},
{"question": "Executable PNGs", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "The YAML file of Prometheus Operator has over 13k lines, one of the longest YAML files on GitHub ever", "details": "", "answers": ["YAML is the bane of our existence.  I think in 10 years we will look at YAML and decide that it was a mistake,  maybe even more than XML.We badly need a simpler, well defined configuration format to take over and for configuration file formats to stop being used for coding,  especially imperative style coding."]},
{"question": "Coding interview questions set 5 with javascript solution.", "details": "", "answers": []},
{"question": "Making an x86 OS - Update, Resources, Future of the Series", "details": "", "answers": ["It's nice to know people are still trying to make fresh new operating systems out there.Even if they're relatively primitive."]},
{"question": "Scott Hanselman's 2021 Ultimate Developer and Power Users Tool List for Windows", "details": "", "answers": [""]},
{"question": "How to make an accurate estimate? You don't.", "details": "", "answers": ["You don'tYup.\u00a0The amount of dev time organizations spend on estimates that are a waste of company money absolutely blows my mind.  This is especially bad in orgs littered with .   The part that kills me is that PMPs run this failed playbook repeatedly and the organization is inclined to blame the engineering group for not predicting the unknown unknowns correctly.  I guess PMPs sort of come by it honestly as 30% of software projects are quite predictable. Sadly, that's just enough sucksess to keep the confirmation bias going for years to come."]}
]